<root>
  <total>43974</total>
  <columns>DC_TITLE_BOOK,DC_TITLE_CBOOK,DC_DN_SKETCH,DC_DN_CSKETCH,DC_CR_AUTHOR,DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE,DC_ST_3RD</columns>
  <book id="67733">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Sarah Coffin</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>梵克雅宝（Van Cleef &amp; Arpels）是一个具有百年历史的著名珠宝品牌。自从梵克雅宝1906年在法国凡登广场成立以来，其在奢侈珠宝的风格设置和设计趋势上就扮演了领导角色。这本书探索了梵克雅宝对于20世纪珠宝设计所做贡献的历史意义，介绍了逾250件梵克雅宝在世界各博物馆和私人收藏中的最著名的作品，包括珠宝、腕表、时尚配饰和艺术精品，并且伴随2011年二月在纽约史密森学会举办的大型展览出版。本书由6篇浅显易懂的文章和近300张照片组成，还收录了从梵克雅宝档案中获取的从未发表过的设计图纸。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Since its opening on the Place Vendome in 1906, the jeweler Van Cleef &amp; Arpels has played a leading role in setting style and design trends in luxury jewelry. &amp;quot,Set in Style&amp;quot, explores the historical significance of the firms contributions to jewelry design in the 20th century. The book features more than 250 of Van Cleef &amp; Arpels most celebrated works from museum and private collections worldwide, including jewels, timepieces, fashion accessories and objets dart and is published to acco</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Thames &amp; Hudson Ltd</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>Set in Style: The Jewelry of Van Cleef &amp; Arpels</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>风格设置：梵克雅宝珠宝</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67734">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Eliot Siegel</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>这是一个不可或缺的成为专业时尚摄影师的指南，从组织一次时尚拍摄到向潜在客户展示你的作品，这个关于时尚摄影的实用基础课程提供了有关原则、实践和技术的关键建议。这本书不仅仅是介绍摄影的技术方面，而且将会帮助读者发展他们自己的独特艺术风格。所有学摄影的学生以及任何对杂志或促销品设计感兴趣的读者都会发现这本书是一个宝贵的参考工具。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>An indispensable guide to becoming a professional fashion photographer, from organizing a fashion shoot to presenting your portfolio to a potential client.This practical foundation course in fashion photography offers key advice on the principles, practice and techniques of the subject. Dealing with far more than just the technical aspects of photography, this book will help the reader to evolve a unique artistic style of their own. All photography students, as well as anyone interested in magaz</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Thames &amp; Hudson Ltd</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>The Fashion Photography Course: First Principles to Successful Shoot - the Essential Guide</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>时尚摄影课程:成功拍摄的首要原则——重要指南</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67735">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Matt Bua</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书集结全球天才建筑师、设计师及艺术家的作品，通过产品或生存环境的评论准确传达什么是建筑替代物。这些作品已在网络组织“画建筑”（drawingbuilding.org）上经过了长期广泛的收集。艺术家通过绘图展现了他们对于结构的惊人的视觉研究，将目光及思想专注于现存制造渠道和设计惯例之外的范畴。根本性的主题通过视觉想象与表达得以探讨，包括：科技可持续性、栖息地、小型社区、堡垒要塞等。现在的想象则是未来的种子，本书全新的想象视野，适合任何一位从人文情感上及造型实践上对我们的生存未来感兴趣的读者。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Born out of the drawingbuilding.org online archive, Architectural Inventions presents a stunning visual study of impossible or speculative structures that exist only on paper. Soliciting the work of architects, designers, and artists of renownas well as emerging talents from all over the worldMaximilian Goldfarb and Matt Bua have gathered an array of works that convey architectural alternatives, through products, expansions, or critiques of our inhabited environments. From abstract and conceptua</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Laurence King Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>Architectural Inventions: Visionary Drawings</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>建筑学发明：有远见的绘画</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67736">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Karolyn Kiisel</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>立体裁剪（Draping）是指用棉细布在人偶模特上设计出时装，这也是每位设计师必备的技能。在本书中，凯洛琳•齐塞尔（Karolyn Kiisel）介绍了一系列经典服装款式的制作过程，旨在循序渐进地传授裁剪的基本知识和高级技能。基础知识包括确定服装款式、用针固定、修改剪裁，到运用折叠、褶皱使衣服定形及处理复杂的曲线。高级技能则包括恰当使用垫肩、衬裙等附属工具，以及处理不平衡的裁剪。本书最后还独辟一章，为读者介绍了即兴的剪裁技巧。书涉及的每个技能和知识点均附有详细的说明图片和生动的立体线条图，有志于立体裁剪的读者必能从此书中获益不浅。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Draping is the art of using cotton muslin to create a fashion design directly on a mannequin. It is an essential skill for fashion designers. In this book, Karolyn Kiisel presents a series of step-by-step projects, creating real garments in classic styles, that are designed to develop skills from the most basic to more advanced techniques. Starting with the basics of choosing and preparing the dress form for draping, the book advances through pinning, trimming and clipping, and creating shape us</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Laurence King Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>Draping: The Complete Course</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>立体裁剪教程</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67737">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>William H Jordy</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Historian and architectural critic William H. Jordy (1917-1997) significantly shaped the way we understand the character and meaning of modern architecture and American culture. This collection of his thought-provoking essays encompasses Jordy&amp;#39,s entire career and includes his signature essay, &amp;quot,The Symbolic Essence of Modern Architecture of the Twenties and Its Continuing Influence&amp;quot,. The collection also contains critical writings on works by Ludwig Mies van der Rohe, Le Corbusier, L</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Yale University Press</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>&amp;quot,Symbolic Essence&amp;quot, and Other Writings on Modern Architecture and American Culture</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67738">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Rowan Moore, Kevin Rhowbotham, Mark Harrison</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>霍金斯/布朗（Hawkins/Brown）是一个主要活跃于伦敦的建筑师团体，它被视为当今最富活力的年轻建筑团体之一。这本带有大量插图的书籍审视该公司负责的当代建筑中的重要项目，探索它们的创意、多样性和韧性。其中涉及的项目包括为亨利·摩尔基金会（Henry Moore Foundation）设计的备受赞誉的新美术馆，为雕塑家雷切尔·怀特瑞德（Rachel Whiteread）设计的工作室以及注重可持续发展的建筑项目如伦敦的女性先驱中心（Womens Pioneer Centre）等。霍金斯/布朗是英国建筑业的先锋，他们因融合想象力和实用性于一体的风格而闻名。无论是为现存建筑带来新活力，还是建造全新建筑，每一次设计都充满特色，注重客户和社区的需求。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Hawkins\Brown are London based architects who have been described as  one of the most exciting young practices of today. (Architecture Today). This extensively illustrated book considers key projects in terms of contemporary architecture, exploring their creativity, diversity and tenacity. Projects covered include the acclaimed new gallery for the Henry Moore Foundation, studio space for the sculptor Rachel Whiteread, as well as projects that focus on sustainability in architecture, as with the </DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Black Dog Publishing Ltd</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>&amp;Also</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>&amp;\和</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67739">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Tom Dixon, Maria Helena Estrada,</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>继2002年《汤匙设计》一书得到成功之后，Phaiton再出《餐刀设计》，展示了10位一流设计专家挑选的全球100名最重要的年轻产品设计师和他们的作品。该书甫一出版便成为一部综合的、不可或缺的当今全球创意产品设计专著。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Following the success of Spoon in 2002, &amp; Fork presents 10 leading design experts&amp;#39, choice of 100 of the most important young product designers from around the world. The result is a comprehensive, must-have survey of today&amp;#39,s most innovative international product design.</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Phaidon</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>&amp;Fork</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>餐刀设计</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67740">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Peter Kennard</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《链接地球》在内容和形式上均具有革命性的意义，书中不含文字，而是用照片叙述代替了语言去讲故事。Peter Kennar便是如此激进的艺术家，他的作品不断地质问着权力结构和非正义的问题，书中收录了艺术家20世纪80年代的反核主题作品，以及他对伊拉克和阿富汗战争作出回应的作品，内含有七个章节的图片故事，包括艺术家最新的作品。本书是艺术家40年艺术生涯的结晶，此次出版也义正词严地提出艺术家对人类迫在眉睫的生态危机、军备竞赛、国际非正义权力结构等严峻问题的思考。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>@earth is as revolutionary in form as it is in content. It contains no words: instead it tells its story in the universal language of photomontage, long the favoured medium of radical artists. Peter Kennard is one such, whose work has consistently questioned power structures and injustice, from his anti-nuclear works of the 1980s to his powerful works in response to the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. @earth is a photo-essay in seven chapters, combining new works, made together with Tarek Salhany,</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Tate Publishing Ltd</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>(At) Earth</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>链接地球</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67742">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>William E.Wallace</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《米开朗基罗:&amp;quot,雕塑•绘画•建筑&amp;quot,作品全集》内容简介：国内首度引进，最权威米开朗基罗作品全集,•完整呈现米开朗基罗所有现存且来源毫无争议作品,•讲述文艺复兴三杰之一 “米开朗基罗”的曲折艺术生涯及人生经历,•透过大师最传世作品体会一个充满真实人性的米开朗基罗,&lt;•全方位、多角度、从整体到局部完整展现了米开朗基罗作品的原貌,•纯手工装订、8开巨幅呈现、45g圣经纸插页完美展现、进口超净白雪纺铜版纸数码精印，极致震撼价198元，年度最超值作品倾情奉献,米开朗基罗，意大利文艺复兴时期伟大的雕塑家、绘画家、建筑师和诗人，文艺复兴时期雕塑艺术最高峰的代表。米开朗基罗的雕塑作品以人体作为表达感情的主要手段，其作品刚劲有力、气魄宏大，充分体现了文艺复兴时期生气勃勃的人文主义精神。1498年，年仅23岁的米开朗基罗开始为罗马圣彼得大教堂创作大理石群雕像《罗马圣殇》，作品一问世，立即引起轰动，这是他一生中唯一署名的作品。1501年，26岁的米开朗基罗开始创作他另一举世闻名的杰作———《大卫》。《大卫》不仅仅是一尊雕像，而是文艺复兴人文主义思想在艺术上得到充分体现的象征。此外，在米开朗</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《米开朗基罗:&amp;quot,雕塑•绘画•建筑&amp;quot,作品全集》内容简介：国内首度引进，最权威米开朗基罗作品全集,•完整呈现米开朗基罗所有现存且来源毫无争议作品,•讲述文艺复兴三杰之一 “米开朗基罗”的曲折艺术生涯及人生经历,•透过大师最传世作品体会一个充满真实人性的米开朗基罗,&lt;•全方位、多角度、从整体到局部完整展现了米开朗基罗作品的原貌,•纯手工装订、8开巨幅呈现、45g圣经纸插页完美展现、进口超净白雪纺铜版纸数码精印，极致震撼价198元，年度最超值作品倾情奉献,米开朗基罗，意大利文艺复兴时期伟大的雕塑家、绘画家、建筑师和诗人，文艺复兴时期雕塑艺术最高峰的代表。米开朗基罗的雕塑作品以人体作为表达感情的主要手段，其作品刚劲有力、气魄宏大，充分体现了文艺复兴时期生气勃勃的人文主义精神。1498年，年仅23岁的米开朗基罗开始为罗马圣彼得大教堂创作大理石群雕像《罗马圣殇》，作品一问世，立即引起轰动，这是他一生中唯一署名的作品。1501年，26岁的米开朗基罗开始创作他另一举世闻名的杰作———《大卫》。《大卫》不仅仅是一尊雕像，而是文艺复兴人文主义思想在艺术上得到充分体现的象征。此外，在米开朗</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>北京美术摄影出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>米开朗基罗雕塑.绘画.建筑作品全集</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>“雕塑·绘画·建筑”作品全集: 米开朗基罗</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67743">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>浙江大学出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>宋画全集：第二卷第二册.上海博物馆藏品第二册（精装版）</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>《宋画全集》第二卷第二册-上海博物馆藏品第二册</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67744">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>浙江大学出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>宋画全集：第二卷第一册.上海博物馆藏品第一册（精装版）</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>《宋画全集》第二卷第一册-上海博物馆藏品第一册</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67745">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>宋画全集编辑委员会</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>浙江大学出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>《宋画全集》第六卷第六册-欧美其它收藏机构藏品</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>《宋画全集》第六卷第六册-欧美其它收藏机构藏品</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67746">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>浙江大学出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>宋画全集：第七卷第二册.日本各收藏机构藏品（红木版）</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>《宋画全集》第七卷第二册（日本各收藏机构藏品）</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67747">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>浙江大学出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>宋画全集：第三卷第二册.辽宁省博物馆藏品第二册（精装版）</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>《宋画全集》第三卷第二册-辽宁省博物馆藏品第二册</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67748">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>浙江大学出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>宋画全集：第三卷第一册.辽宁省博物馆藏品第一册（精装版）</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>《宋画全集》第三卷第一册-辽宁省博物馆藏品第一册</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67749">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>浙江大学出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>宋画全集：第一卷第八册.北京故宫博物院藏品第八册（精装版）</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>《宋画全集》第一卷第八册（北京故宫博物院藏品第八册)精装版</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67750">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>浙江大学出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>宋画全集：第一卷第二册.北京故宫博物院藏品第二册（精装版）</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>《宋画全集》第一卷第二册-北京故宫博物院藏品第二册</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67751">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>浙江大学出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>宋画全集：第一卷第六册.北京故宫博物院藏品第六册（精装版）</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>《宋画全集》第一卷第六册（北京故宫博物院藏品第六册)精装版</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67752">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>浙江大学出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>宋画全集：第一卷第七册.北京故宫博物院藏品第七册（精装版）</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>《宋画全集》第一卷第七册（北京故宫博物院藏品第七册)精装版</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67753">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>浙江大学出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>宋画全集：第一卷第三册.北京故宫博物院藏品第三册（精装版）</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>《宋画全集》第一卷第三册（北京故宫博物院藏品第三册）精装版</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67754">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>浙江大学出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>宋画全集：第一卷第四册.北京故宫博物院藏品第四册（精装版）</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>《宋画全集》第一卷第四册（北京故宫博物院藏品第四册)精装版</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67755">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>浙江大学出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>宋画全集：第一卷第五册.北京故宫博物院藏品第五册（精装版）</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>《宋画全集》第一卷第五册（北京故宫博物院藏品第五册)精装版</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67756">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《宋画全集》由画像与文献两部分组成，是一部工具性质的大型宋代绘画总集。由于时代与风格承应关系，五代和辽、金作品也列入编纂范围。入编作品均为纸本和绢本绘画，壁画、版画和石刻画等其他材料的绘画作品暂不收录。全集卷分图像七卷，文献一卷，每卷依规模分册。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>浙江大学出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>宋画全集：第一卷第一册.北京故宫博物院藏品第一册（精装版）</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>《宋画全集》第一卷第一册-北京故宫博物院藏品第一册</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67757">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>中国艺术史上若论绘画，宋元的重要性绝对最常被特别标志出来，而对于元代绘画的整理与收罗，又明显少于宋代作品。在从搜集的广度、编辑的深度、学术诠释支撑的厚度，到印刷工艺考究的精密度，前一套《宋画全集》，已在收藏界与学术界都广受好评。较之宋画更少完备整理的元画题材此次出版，又绝对是中国艺术当代出版的历史事件级藏书。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>中國藝術史上若論繪畫，宋元的重要性絕對最常被特別標誌出來，而對於元代繪畫的整理與收羅，又明顯少於宋代作品。在從蒐集的廣度、編輯的深度、學術詮釋支撐的厚度，到印刷工藝考究的精密度，前一套《宋畫全集》，已在收藏界與學術界都廣受好評。較之宋畫更少完備整理的元畫題材此次出版，又絕對是中國藝術當代出版的歷史事件級藏書。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>浙江大学出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>《元画全集》第一卷第一册</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>《元画全集》第一卷第一册</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67758">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Gerardo Mosquera</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书主要探讨摄影中的身份构建，编者将托马斯•拉夫（Thomas Ruff）和辛迪•谢尔曼（Cindy Sherman）这两位当代艺术大师和一位19世纪默默无名的摄影师弗兰克•蒙特罗（Frank Montero）的作品加以比较。谢尔曼的作品为我们展示了一个可以衍生出万千个面孔的脸庞，与之相反，托马斯则致力于抹去人的色彩，故而其作品所有面部特征也基本磨灭殆尽，到了蒙特罗那里，人脸则成为了一个历经时间磨练而独立的存在。本书系蒙特罗作品的首次出版，其创作虽不具明显的艺术意图与野心，却能为我们了解拉夫和谢尔曼的作品提供一种恰如其分的伦勃朗式的标尺，进而深入理解肖像摄影和身份构建的奥妙之处。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>&amp;quot,1 Faces/ Faces/One Face&amp;quot, unites two great contemporary artists who have interrogated constructions of identity with an entirely unknown late-nineteenth-century photographer named Frank Montero. Its thesis runs as follows: in Cindy Sherman&amp;#39,s manipulations of generic casting we encounter a face that produces all faces, in Thomas Ruff&amp;#39,s proliferating but depersonalized portraits, we all encounter all faces reduced to a zero degree, and in Montero, we encounter a face that plays t</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>La Fábrica Editorial</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1.000 Caras/0 Caras/1rostro</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>托马斯•拉夫，辛迪•谢尔曼和弗兰克•蒙特罗</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67759">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Aaron Betsky, Roger Connah, Haig Beck, Jackie Cooper, Kristin Feireiss, Jorge Glusberg, Tom Heneghan, Mohsen Mostafavi, Terence Riley, Jaime Salazar</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《10 x 10》以多样的视角看待当今世界的新建筑，由10名顶尖国际建筑馆长和评论家精选出了100位建筑师新秀。每个评论家都会精心列出10个文化参考——包括设计的物品、书籍、录影、主题和运转——来展示当今设计界的动态影响力。本书是独一无二的建筑出版物，真正提供了最具想象力、最重要的当今或未来设计师的全方位视角。全书468页，包含1500多幅惊人的图片。本书还专门涵盖了1990年至今的250个建筑和工程，如花费百万的日本横滨国际港口码头、小成本的挪威里瑟尔避暑别墅和古根海姆虚拟博物馆的数字世界。书中还有建筑观点的碰撞：每个评论家都会为其挑选的建筑师写一篇随笔，或者挑战其他评论家挑出的人选，并给出其对当今建筑界发展趋势的观点。《10 x 10》不仅是不可或缺的资料书，还是迎接建筑界未来的终极设计项目。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>10 x 10 is a kaleidoscopic view of new architecture in the world today. 100 emerging architects have been selected by 10 leading international architecture curators and critics. Each critic has also selected and listed 10 cultural references - including designed objects, books, films, themes, and movements - to reveal a dynamic range of influences in today&amp;#39,s design environment. The book is unique in architectural publishing and provides a truly global view of the most imaginative and importa</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Phaidon</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>10 X 10: 10 Critics, 100 Architects</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>10ⅹ10：10个评论家，100个建筑师</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67760">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Emmanuel Cooper</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>陶器制作是最早、亦是分布最广的一项人类活动，最早的历史可以溯及石器时代。本书是换上软装折页封面和新设计的精美书套后出版的大英博物馆参考资料，是个从史前至今的全球瓷器艺术与产品的一个经典而全面的彩页概览，对于学生或任何陶器爱好者而言就像是一个信息的宝矿。书中的叙述起于近东与中东最早期的文化，继之则依陶器制品的发展年代绕行全球。最后一章则分析了从20世纪初至今作为艺术家与陶艺工作室个人表达媒介的陶器发展。艾曼纽·库柏(Emmanuel Cooper)是国际知名的陶艺家、作家、评论家和广播主持，同时也是声誉卓著、举足轻重的杂志《陶器评论》的编辑，他关于现代与历史陶器方面的著作丰富多样，所涉甚广。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Lavishly illustrated and extremely comprehensive ...a bargain&amp;#39, - &amp;quot,Antiques Magazine&amp;quot,. &amp;#39,The evolution of pottery ...is fascinating, and this book does it justice&amp;#39, - &amp;quot,The Good Book Guide&amp;quot,. &amp;#39,An epic tale ...a book to buy and to treasure&amp;#39, - &amp;quot,Crafts Magazine&amp;quot,. This is the definitive British Museum reference book reissued with a beautiful new jacket design and pbk-with-flaps cover. This is the classic, comprehensive, colour survey of ceramic art and pr</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>The British Museum Press</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>10,000 Years of Pottery</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>陶瓷10000年</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67761">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Ed.Jurgen Muller</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>这是塔森出版社为你开出的必看片单，它们无一例外是二十世纪电影史上的佳作，不仅包括《大都会》、《摩登时代》、《公民凯恩》，《七武士》、《甜蜜生活》、《教父》、《安妮·霍尔》、《蓝丝绒》、《低俗小说》等这些大师佳作，也有《被遗忘的人们》这类小众电影。恐怖片、爱情片、西部片、音乐剧、悲喜剧、冒险、史诗，还有黑色电影，新浪潮等这些类型电影都涵盖其中。书中以年代的次序，介绍了每一部影片的大致情况，包括剧情梗概，演职人员表，技术信息，花絮和奖项，当然还保留了每部电影的剧照和海报。本书在以十年为节点的章节之前还有对时代背景的介绍，总之，这是一次具有历史感的对胶片时代的缅怀。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This title covers your favorite flicks. This is our choice of must-see masterpieces. They say that in life, there are winners and there are losers. Though the movies we selected for this two-volume collection are winners indeed, those that didn&amp;#39,t make the cut aren&amp;#39,t losers. We just didn&amp;#39,t like them quite as much. It was a tough, soul-searching process, but after much debate and deliberation Taschen settled on what we believe to be the 100 finest examples of 20th century filmmaking. F</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Taschen GmbH</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 All-Time Favorite Movies</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>100部永不过时的电影</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67762">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Zahid Sardar</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《100辆最棒的自行车》里列出的是目前世界上可以找到的最棒的自行车，让那些各种类型的自行车爱好者大开眼界。无论你是bmxtreme或山地自行车爱好者，旅行车和赛车热衷者，抑或是一个城市的通勤或快递员，再或者只是对自行车创新设计如不断推进的和折叠工程深深着迷的人，这本书都能给你带来独特的东西。此处展出的自行车来自欧洲，东南亚和北美，更别提南半球的例子了。主要的自行车制造商除了Boardman，捷安特（GIANT）和富士（Fuji），也有来自如下品牌的标新立异的材料：Biomega， Calfee 和daymak。《100辆最棒的自行车》对于那些迫不及待想要对这些各种类自行车的优秀设计和工程有所了解的人都是必备的基本资源。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>These are the best bikes to be found anywhere right now, giving every kind of cyclist an overview of what is out there. Whether a BMXtreme or mountain bike enthusiast, a keen tourer or racer, a city commuter or courier, or simply fascinated with the constantly advancing mechanics and engineering of folding and other innovative bike designs, this book has something for you. The bikes on display come from across Europe, East and South Asia and North America, not to mention examples from the southe</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Laurence King Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Best Bikes</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67763">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>这本书是塔森出版社25期专刊。这是21世纪初当代艺术的综合概要。这个两卷版的书册从塔森特出版的《千禧年的艺术》和《当代艺术》系列丛书中选取了100位最有影响力的艺术家，凝缩成了这本21世纪初当代艺术综合概要。书中选取了各种各样的先锋艺术家的作品，如让•米切尔•巴斯奎特，马莱内•杜马斯， 达明安•赫斯特，麦克•凯利，杰夫•昆斯， 阿尔伯特•厄伦，理查德•普林斯，查尔斯•雷，辛迪•雪曼，克里斯托弗•伍尔以及年轻一代的杰出艺术家格伦•布朗，娜塔莉•尤里贝尔，托马斯•弗里德曼，马克•格罗蒂扬和特伦斯•科赫。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This title is Taschen 25 - Special edition! This is a comprehensive compendium of contemporary art at the beginning of the 21st century. This special two-volume edition compiles the 100 most exciting artists from the seminal Taschen title &amp;quot,Art at the Turn of the Millenium&amp;quot, as well as the renowned &amp;quot,Art Now&amp;quot, series, condensing them to a comprehensive compendium of contemporary art at the beginning of the 21st century. Our selection features a wide variety of works by pioneering</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Taschen GmbH</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Contemporary Artists</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>100个当代艺术家</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67764">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书分为两卷，集合了塔森出版社《时尚风行标》系列的亮点，纵览了21世纪以来全球的时装设计。本书由特里•琼斯（Terry Jones）编辑，是任何对未来时尚感兴趣的读者不可或缺的参考。新晋设计师——明日之星——以及产业巨匠和既定的实践者，包括：海德•艾克曼（Haider Ackermann）、阿瑟丁•阿拉亚（Azzedine Alaïa）、安•迪穆拉米斯特（Ann Demeulemeester）、杜嘉班纳（Dolce &amp; Gabbana）、汤姆•福特（Tom Ford）、让- 保罗- 高提耶（Jean Paul Gaultier）、尼古拉•盖斯奇埃尔（Nicolas Ghesquière）、马克•雅可布（Marc Jacobs）、川久保玲（Rei Kawakubo）、克里斯汀•拉克鲁瓦（Christian Lacroix）、卡尔•拉格菲尔德（Karl Lagerfeld）、马丁•马吉拉（Martin Margiela）、斯特拉•麦卡特尼（Stella McCartney）、亚历山大•麦昆（Alexander McQueen）、罗达特（Rodarte）、德赖斯•范诺顿（Dries Van </DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This two-volume compilation brings together highlights from TASCHEN’s Fashion Now! series to create a comprehensive overview of fashion design around the world at the start of the 21st century. Edited by i-D creator Terry Jones, this book is an indispensible work of reference for anyone interested in the future of fashion. Fast-rising new designers—tomorrow’s superstars—feature alongside industry giants and established practitioners, including
 Haider Ackermann, Azzedine Alaïa, Ann Demeulemeeste</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Taschen GmbH</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Contemporary Fashion Designers</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>100位当代时装设计师</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67765">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Philip Jodidio</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>现今世界上新建的建筑大部分都注重对环境的影响——可持续性，且要比以往消耗更少的能源。建筑是温室气体的主要来源之一，这使得生态友好型建筑更加重要。这本书从《现代建筑》系列和许多我们未曾目睹的项目中带给我们最好的绿色建筑范例。弗兰克•盖里（Frank Gehry）和诺曼•福斯特（Norman Foster）等知名建筑师和来自拉丁美洲、美国、欧洲和亚洲的年轻进取的设计者都在书中讲述了他们的观点。这并不是一本技术书籍，其内容也不非限于任何预设的种类。绿色意味着注重在建造中的责任感和运用现代建筑技术，其实有许多方法来表达环保意识。有一些被称为“消极的”措施，其历史犹如建筑的历史一般长久，而另一些措施则源于前沿技术。本书涵盖了以上两种方法和其他很多实践案例，共收集了100座世界上最新颖的生态友好型建筑。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Eco-friendly building in the world today The most exciting new buildings in the world are now almost all environmentally aware, sustainable, and conceived to consume far less energy than ever before. That architecture is one of the major sources of greenhouse gases in the world makes this new trend all the more significant. This book brings the best examples of green projects from the &amp;quot,Architecture Now! &amp;quot,series together with numerous new, never-seen-before projects. Well-known architec</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Taschen GmbH</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Contemporary Green Buildings</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>100座当代生态建筑</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67766">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Philip Jodidio</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>这本书从智力到克罗地亚及中国记录了当代出色的房屋设计。相比于与公司的合作项目，个人民宅设计给了建筑师更多的自由。构想生活空间是非常具有挑战的。在设计房子时，建筑师们永远寻求着为我们居住的空间和日常生活创新的解决方案。现在环境问题已经成为建造可持续的建筑物一个重要因素，深刻地改变了建筑业。这个两卷本的出版物收集了过去十年间新出道的和已有所成的建筑师设计的100所世界最先进、最引人入胜的房屋，包括约翰•帕森，理查德•迈耶，坂茂，安藤忠雄和扎哈•哈迪德。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This title deals with exceptional contemporary houses from Chile to Croatia to China. Designing private homes offers architects more freedom than corporate projects to express their ideas and try out new concepts. Conceiving living spaces is not without its own set of challenges, for which architects are forever looking for innovative solutions-rethinking the way we inhabit our home and live our daily lives is all part of the job when designing a house. Nowadays environmental concerns have becom</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Taschen GmbH</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Contemporary Houses: Vol 2</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>100栋当代房屋设计（两卷本）</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67767">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Harold Koda</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>哪个女人不愿想象自己穿上漂亮的设计师礼服？大都会美术馆著名的服饰研究院从永久藏品中首次选出100件礼服集结成册，每一件都能体现出时尚如何反映出更宽泛的文化背景。这些独一无二的收藏中包括有保罗•普瓦雷（Paul Poiret）、可可•香奈儿(Coco Chanel)等众多名家的设计，服饰种类繁多、数量惊人。从17世纪末的扣纽礼服到21世纪早期最前沿的裙装，本书为每个时代的美感和超凡勾勒出生动的图景，同时也栩栩如生地讲述了时尚如何变迁（有时这种改变十分剧烈）。1600年代晚期的羊毛礼服、1800年代的大裙撑红绸裙、1920年代闪亮的短舞裙、1950年代的酒会礼服和1960年代的迷你裙——每一件都讲述着那个时代的故事，也证明了时装设计艺术的持久创造力。服装图片伴有丰富的文字说明，更有细节特写、天桥照片、时装样片、艺术作品和设计师照片等为本书增色。最后还有一份相关词汇的术语表。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>What woman can resist imagining herself in a beautiful designer dress? Here, for the first time ever, are 100 fabulous gowns from the permanent collection of the renowned Costume Institute at The Metropolitan Museum of Art, each of which is a reminder of the ways fashion reflects the broader culture that created it. Featuring designs by Paul Poiret, Coco Chanel, Madame Grès, Yves Saint Laurent, Gianni Versace, Vivienne Westwood, Alexander McQueen, and many others, this one-of-a-kind collection p</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Metropolitan Museum of Art</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Dresses</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>服饰研究院：100款礼服</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67768">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Margit J. Mayer</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>这本TASCHEN新版酒店集锦，收录了全球100家十分特别的酒店和客房，从阿布扎比到越南等国家，以两卷的篇幅介绍从床铺、基本早餐到六星级的服务，把下次选择在哪里休息这个问题变成小事一桩。书中从加尔达湖费尔特里内利别墅这般的梦中城堡，到挪威Juvet酒店别致的玻璃门，从地中海带着怀旧情怀的小旅馆和适中的价格，到犹他州峡谷王国昂贵但物有所值的Amangiri度假区，逐一呈现，即使是细心的网络搜客也会被这本书引诱到自己的沙发上，进行一场纸上旅行。而室内设计爱好者可以把此书当作鼓舞人心的华美沙发、床、灯和浴室的全球性精选集合。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Rooms with a view.A collection of 100 heavenly hideaways. 
When traveling for business, we often prefer hotel rooms of the same type in London, Paris, or Shanghai. It s just more convenient. A different set of rules applies when they search for a place to celebrate a special family holiday, a weekend with a new lover, or a few days of blissful solitude with some great books. Suddenly a balcony with postcard-worthy views counts more than the number of TV channels, a sumptuous bed with a heavenly </DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Taschen GmbH</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Getaways Around The World (2 Volume）</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>全球酒店100家</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67769">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Alexander Gnädiger</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>在adidas Originals的赞助下，亚历山大•格内丁格（Alexander Gnädinger）近期发布了其新书《100个宝丽莱女孩》。该书展示了在数码摄影时代十分难得的东西：未被改变的真实。格内丁格捕捉到了这100个女孩对其自身的真实看法，以及她们想要展示给别人的一面——所见，便是所得。该项目在柏林阿迪达斯概念店No.74启动，当时这里正在举行包括1978年的Adria Jeans到2001年的山本耀司等经典款女鞋展览。本书共有476页，突出了250幅照片，封面是由原始宝丽莱纸板制作而成。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>&amp;quot,In search of the lost.&amp;quot, The famous photographer Alexander Gn&amp;#xE4,dinger asked 1 well-known models to stage themselves, how they perceive themselves as beautiful.</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Seltmann, Arno, Frank Seltmann u. Oliver Seltmann</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Girls on Polaroid</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67770">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Richard Weston</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>作者按编年史的体例，将塑造建筑的100个最具影响的创想组织起来，给人启发。这种编写逻辑提供了一种有趣且智能的简史，串联起广泛的资源，引人深究，是一本有趣且触角广泛的入门书。书中涵盖的创想包括启发性和流行性的观念、科技、技法和运动。作者熟知不同文化国家的传统，巧妙而有趣地在文本讲述上进行切换，揭示它们的诞生及影响力。本书装帧轻巧，便于携带，精选角度醒目的摄影图片，以高品质的印刷给读者强烈的现场感。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This inspiring book chronicles the most influential ideas that have shaped architecture. Entertaining and intelligent, it provides a concise history of the subject, and is also a fascinating resource to dip into. Arranged in a broadly chronological order to show the development of architecture, the ideas that comprise the book include innovative and influential concepts, technologies, techniques and movements. Each idea is presented through interesting text and arresting visuals, and explores wh</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Laurence King Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Ideas That Changed Architecture</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>100 个改变建筑的创想</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67771">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Harriet Worsley</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《改变时尚的100个观念》介绍了自1900年至今对西方女性服装产生巨大影响的各种观念。本书生动迷人，阅读过程令人振奋不已，是极富启发性的时尚圣经。通过记录改变女性着装方式的各种事件和观念，本书也对20世纪时尚史进行了叙述。但却并非仅仅是对时尚变化的简单记叙，而是十分出色地解释了这些促使变化发生的原因。从斜纹裁剪和细跟鞋的发明到可可•香奈儿（Coco Chanel）这样改变了人们对服装的看法的伟大设计师，本书既充满愉悦，又充满智慧，阅读过程无疑是一场视觉盛宴。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>100 Ideas That Changed Fashion chronicles the most influential fashion ideas that changed womenswear in the West from 1900 to the present day. The book will be visually arresting, exciting to read and an inspiring fashion bible. By charting the incidents and ideas that changed the way women dress, it will incidentally give a history of 20th century fashion. But rather than just documenting the changes in fashion, it crucially explains why these changes happened. From the invention of the bias cu</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Laurence King Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Ideas That Changed Fashion</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>改变时尚的100个观念</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67772">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>David Parkinson</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>这本极具启发性的图书记录了自电影出现之初至今，对电影产生了重大影响个各种观念。本书既有趣又富有智慧，既是一部电影简史，又是引人入胜的文献材料。书中内容基本按编年次序编排，展示了电影的发展历程，书中介绍的观念包括有创新思想、技术、技法和各种运动。从默片时代的杰作到今天的大片和艺术电影，配图丰富的内页使读者得以发现或重新发现各大洲的电影作品。书中讨论了赋予好莱坞全球电影业霸权的划时代事件，也讨论了像德国表现主义、导演主创论和第三电影等多个主题，对连续性剪辑、类型和声效等关键概念也有全面的研究。每个观念都有渊博的文字和动人的图像加以说明，对运用电影这个媒介的经典名作表达了敬意。读者们可通过本书了解这些观念如何形成和它们对今天的巨大影响。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This inspiring book chronicles the most influential ideas that have shaped film since its inception. Entertaining and intelligent, it provides a concise history as well as being a fascinating resource to dip into. Arranged in a broadly chronological order to show the development of film, the ideas include innovative concepts, technologies, techniques and movements. From the silent eras masterpieces to todays blockbusters and art house movies, these highly illustrated pages are a chance to discov</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Laurence King Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Ideas That Changed Film</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>改变电影的100个观念</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67773">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Steven Heller</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书讲述了创意怎样影响与定义平面设计，以及这些创意理念如何在设计中体现。本书100个条目，按照时间顺序，范围极广，如技术（套印、一次性设计、隔色墨斗），风格（明细的排版、空白），对象（书皮、设计手册），方法（剪纸、像素纹理）等。本书由平面设计领域、当今世界顶级权威编著，书中精选大量经典案例，并进行深度、详细解析，给你无限的设计灵感，具有重要的研读价值。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>New in the &amp;quot,100 Ideas that Changed...&amp;quot, series, this book demonstrates how ideas influenced and defined graphic design, and how those ideas have manifested themselves in objects of design. The 100 entries, arranged broadly in chronological order, range from technical (overprinting, rub-on designs, split fountain), to stylistic (swashes on caps, loud typography, and white space), to objects (dust jackets, design handbooks), and methods (paper cut-outs, pixelation). Written by one of the </DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Laurence King Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Ideas That Changed Graphic Design</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67774">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Mary Warner Marien</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>从十九世纪初的银版照相法到今天的数字革命浪潮，摄影的发展令人瞩目。本书按时间顺序详尽地记载了一百个对摄影发展有着深刻影响的观念，包括创新的理念，重要的历史事件，技术进步和社会运动的影响等。编者采用图文并茂的方式为读者介绍了每个思想观念的形成过程和后续影响。生动有趣的文字和不忍释手的作品，必能为您带来一场摄影的思想盛宴。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This compelling book chronicles the most influential ideas that have shaped photography from the invention of the daguerreotype in the early 19th century up to the digital revolution and beyond. Entertaining and intelligent, it provides a fascinating resource to dip into. Arranged in a broadly chronological order to show the development of photography, the ideas that comprise the book include innovative concepts, cultural and social incidents, technologies and movements. Each idea is presented t</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Laurence King Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Ideas That Changed Photography</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>100个改变摄影的创想</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67775">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书在竞争激烈的插画领域精选了最杰出的插画。这本书中的插画家就是从当今世界最成功和最重要的插画家中选取的。史蒂文•海勒（ Steven Heller）完成了从600个插画家中选取100个最重要的插画家这个颇有挑战性的工作。筛选出来的插画家如伊思万•拜雅，加里•贝斯曼，西摩•切瓦斯特，保罗•戴维斯，布莱德•霍兰，米克•伊利，阿妮塔•昆兹和克里斯多夫•尼曼，为我们呈现了动态的和多样的当代插画概况。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>The biggest players in the highly competitive field of illustration
Culled from our Illustration Now! series is this selection of today s most successful and important illustrators from around the globe. In his introduction, Steven Heller fleshes out the challenging process of narrowing down a field of 600 illustrators to a selection of the 100 most significant. The final cut, including artists such as Istvan Banyai, Gary Baseman, Seymour Chwast, Paul Davis, Brad Holland, Mirko Ili , Anita Kunz,</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Taschen GmbH</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Illustrators</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>100个插画家</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67776">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>正值25周年,  TASCHEN以此纪念版图书,为设计迷奉上的一份完美礼物。100种最特别、最激奋人心的室内设计，是一众顶级室内摄影师分头行动，从六大洲精心选择且华丽拍摄而来，从质朴的极简主义到温文尔雅的折衷主义，几乎涵括全球范围内具有代表性的现代风格。读完这本图文并茂的书，你将发现构成这些动人心扉的居所的元素，它们是：真实性、对细节的爱、永不过时的对个体表达的热忱。阅毕此书，无论你处于哪个阶层，你都会重新审视自己的房子，开始学习如何住得更好的艺术。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>How to live well? This is a diverse and inspiring selection of interiors from around the world. This special edition rounds up the creme de la creme of today&amp;#39,s most exceptional and inspiring interiors around the world. Making stops in North and South America, Europe, Asia, and Africa, this painstakingly picked and sumptuously photographed selection of 100 homes represents TASCHEN&amp;#39,s favorite ways people are decorating their dwellings these days.</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Taschen GmbH</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Interiors Around the World</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>100种世界顶级装潢 (两卷本)</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67777">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Sibylle Weber am Bach</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>摩根图书博物馆素来以其著名和精美的素描馆藏著称于世。本书配合其现慕尼黑现代艺术博物馆的国家艺术收藏（Staatliche Graphische Sammlung München）展览出版，介绍了从15到20世纪的100幅素描大师作品。书中展现了摩根馆藏的丰富内容和优良品质，其中既有经过精心创作的细致作品，也有信手拈来的随意创作。它们都是欧洲大师们的卓越杰作，涉及的人物有丁托列托（Tintoretto）、普桑（Poussin）、戈雅（Goya）等，主要的创作类型包括银笔画、粉笔画、钢笔画和水粉画。书中还饶有趣味地介绍了一些摩根馆藏的由来历史。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>The Morgan Library and Museum houses one of the finest and most renowned drawing collections in the world. This publication accompanies the exhibition by the Staatliche Graphische Sammlung München in the Pinakothek der Moderne and shows 100 master drawings from the 15th to the 20th century. Ranging from elaborate tableaux sketches to spontaneous studies, the books holds a rich spectrum of drawings picked, as the most distinguished, from the vast Morgan collection. Techniques evident in the antho</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Hirmer Verlag</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Master Drawings From The Morgan Library &amp; Museum</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>摩根图书博物馆的100幅大师素描</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67778">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Francesca Gavin</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书汇集一百位1970年后出生，在当今艺术圈内颇具影响力的艺术新秀，涵盖了马德里、雅典、洛杉矶、巴黎、柏林、圣保罗等地的全球艺术家，如纽约的阿加特•斯诺（Agathe Snow），柏林的新晋地下艺术家奥兹拉•阿尔通（Ozlem Altin）和斯门•约拿（Sven Johne），以及日本的装置艺术工作者金氏彻平（Teppei Kaneuji）。书中涉及的艺术类型包括绘画、雕塑、装置艺术、摄影、行为艺术、拼贴、电影和新技术等，旨在为读者呈现当代艺术最前沿的主题、创意和表现手法。通过这100位艺术新秀的最新动态，未来的审美理念可由此预见。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Featuring artists born after 1970 this book brings together the people who are creating the aesthetics of the next decade. These are artists who have passed the post-art school no man s land and are making waves in the contemporary art world. It includes an innovative new generation of artists who work on a global scale from Madrid to Athens, Los Angeles to Paris, Berlin to SAo Paulo. There are members of the Bowery school of New York s Lower East Side such as Agathe Snow, the new wave of underg</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Laurence King Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 New Artists</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>100位艺术新秀</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67779">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Harold Koda , Sarah Jessica Parker</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>大都会美术馆服饰研究院继2010年的“100款礼服”之后，再次出版其著名的永久藏品，介绍其丰富的鞋类收藏。本书介绍从16世纪到21世纪的100双鞋，它们生动地展现了时尚变迁，也呈现出历史上不断重现的潮流。例如，15至17世纪的威尼斯女性和1800年代的中国满洲女性都穿厚底鞋。1930年代，萨尔瓦多•菲拉格慕（Salvatore Ferragamo）设计了现代版厚底鞋，更新的样式出现于1970年代和1990年代。本书设计优美、制作精良，展示了各种时髦鞋类。其中有马诺罗•伯拉尼克(Manolo Blahnik)、克里斯汀•鲁布坦 (Christian Louboutin)、罗杰•维威耶（Roger Vivier）和薇薇恩•韦斯特伍德(Vivienne Westwood)的设计。图片伴有丰富的解说，更有艺术品、同时代照片和设计师的肖像，使内容增色不少。本书细诉几世纪以来女性如何利用这些时尚饰品提升格调和地位，无疑能为喜欢时尚设计的读者带来灵感。莎拉•杰西卡•帕克（Sarah Jessica Parker）撰写的前言令本书更易阅读、更有吸引力。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>In a brilliant follow-up to &amp;quot,100 Dresses&amp;quot,, published in 2010, the Costume Institute of the Metropolitan Museum once again opens the vaults of its renowned permanent collection to introduce readers to the rich diversity of shoes within its holdings. This title presents a hundred pairs of shoes, from the 16th to the 21st century, that paint a vivid picture of how styles have changed - sometimes radically - over the years. They also reveal how some trends have reappeared throughout the ag</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Metropolitan Museum of Art</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Shoes</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>服饰研究院：100双鞋</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67780">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Joe La Pommpe</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>广告是一门令人惊叹的艺术，它可以创造数十亿美元的收入，让成千上万的观众成为快乐的消费者。乔•拉庞贝氏（Joe La Pompe）是法国著名的广告大师，也是一名热心的博客作者，在他看来，成功广告运用的视觉语言并无神秘之处。在本书中，乔•拉庞贝氏精选100个全球广为流传的视觉艺术理念和经典广告主题加以深入剖析，为读者探讨其灵感来源，如符号、历史、小说等。通过书中收录的1000个优秀广告作品，读者可充分体会视觉艺术撩动人心、进而影响行动的魅力所在。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>In 100 Visual Ideas, 1000 Great Ads, the French blogger and undercover advertising expert Joe La Pompe exposes the not-so-secret visual recipes behind successful ads. La Pompe extracts the 100 most popular visual ideas and recurring subjects from the world of advertising. He then presents the ten best campaigns from around the world that are based on each of these themes, yet have implemented them in a variety of different ways. By illustrating correlations and inspirations, this book offers adv</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Die Gestalten Verlag</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Visual Ideas, 1000 Great Ads</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>How Advertising Recycles and Hijacks World Famous Symbols and Images</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67781">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Kelly Grovier</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>就如毕加索（Picasso）的《格尔尼卡》（Guernica）和席里柯（Gericault）的《梅杜莎之筏》（Raft of the Medusa）都是他们那个时代的文化丰碑一般，在我们这个年代，也会出现流芳百世的伟大作品。本书收录了诗人、历史学家、文化评论家凯利•格罗米尔（Kelly Grovier）所精心挑选的一百幅完成于1989-2009年间的优秀艺术作品，涵盖绘画、雕塑、装置、表演和视频等多种类型。作者不仅分析了艺术家们（如马修•巴尼、杰夫•昆斯和艾未未等）是如何捕捉从柏林墙坍塌到阿拉伯之春以来的历史动荡与时代精神，更为每幅作品提供了参考图像和简介文字，以追溯其诞生与影响，使读者不仅能走进艺术家的想象之中，更能清晰洞察我们所生存的时代。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Just as Picasso Guernica or Gicault Raft of the Medusa survive as powerful cultural documents of their time, there will be works from our own era that will endure for generations to come. But which ones? Which contemporary artworks best capture the zeitgeist of the late 20th and early 21st centuries? This bold and engaging book, written by one of the freshest and most exciting new voices in cultural criticism, predicts which artists and artworks from the past two decades will come to define our </DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Thames &amp; Hudson Ltd</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Works of Art That Will Define Our Age</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>定义当代的一百幅杰作</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67782">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Neil Bingham</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书汇集300幅二十世纪最知名建筑师的最佳建筑绘图，包括弗兰克•劳埃德•赖特、勒•柯布西耶、路德维希•密斯•凡德罗、弗兰克•盖里以及扎哈•哈迪德等，对建筑绘图历史及建筑史本身都做了深入探讨。丰富的材料按照时间顺序，分为5个章节叙述，提炼出每个时代的风格趋势，使阅读感受更清晰精准。无论是建筑从业者，建筑系学生，或手绘爱好者，都能从本书中获得真知与乐趣。作者尼尔•宾厄姆（Neil Bingham）为伦敦皇家艺术学院顾问，曾是英国建筑皇家学会建筑绘图馆长，长期专注于建筑和设计史的研究及写作。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This beautiful book brings together 300 of the best architectural drawings from the last century by the world&amp;#39,s most prestigious architects, creating both a history of the genre and a survey of twentieth-century architecture. The book is divided into five chronological sections that are prefaced by short essays that highlight the trends and styles of that period. Each drawing is captioned with key information about the architect, the project and the drawing. Architects whose work features in</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Laurence King Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Years of Architectural Drawing: 1900-2000</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>建筑绘图100年：1900-2000</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67783">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Cally Blackman</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书以丰富的图片记录了时尚史上最激动人心、最多姿多彩的一段时期：1900至今天，涵盖上流社会、制服、运动服装、街头服饰和高级定制。将是对时尚服饰爱好者和学生们的最佳选择。过去百余年见证了女性时装的巨大转变。20世纪早期的紧身衣让位给宽松的风尚，例如那由法国时装设计师保罗•普瓦雷（Paul Poiret）掀起的风格热潮。女性生活中两次世界大战的阴影下发生了巨大变化，女性服装也随之变更。从自制服装到高级成衣，从定量配给到“新形象”，从青少年文化到大规模生产，从上流社会到名流文化。本书收录了400余幅照片和插图，当中不少还是第一次出版，将以最具品位和格调的方式为读者们呈现时尚革命的历史。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This book documents in pictures the most exciting and diverse period in fashion: from 1900 to today, covering high society, uniforms, sportswear, streetwear and couture. It will appeal to everyone with an interest in fashion as well as students. The last hundred or so years bore witness to the transformation of womens fashion. The restrictive corsetry of the early twentieth century gave way to looser styles such as those made fashionable by French fashion designer Paul Poiret. As womens lives ch</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Laurence King Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Years of Fashion</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>百年时尚</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67784">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Cally Blackman</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书是由作家兼时尚设计与艺术历史讲师凯利·布莱克曼所著，作者现任职于学府中央圣马丁学院，教授时尚历史与理论课程。书中囊括了400多幅精美绝伦的图画，给读者带来了一场视觉盛宴，同时也是对上个世纪的流派的一次综合调研。通过当今最伟大的插画家的看法，本书还概述了时尚的发展历程。本书对于艺术和时尚界的专业人士来说是极其珍贵的资源，对于世界各地的读者来说也是十分漂亮的设计标本。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>A visual feast of 400 dazzling images, this is a comprehensive survey of the genre over the last century. The book also offers an overview of the development of fashion, as seen through the eyes of the greatest illustrators of the day. An invaluable resource for art and fashion professionals and a beautiful design object for consumers everywhere.</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Laurence King Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Years of Fashion Illustration</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>时尚插画100年</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67785">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Cally Blackman</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书由时尚历史学家凯丽·布拉克曼（Cally Blackman）撰文，为读者呈现男装100年间的巨变。书中包括大量罕见的精美照片，见证了萨维尔街的优雅剪裁以及卡其、丹宁布制服乃至多样的风格和色彩表现。书中既有好莱坞的时尚偶像，也有1930年代的知名艺术家的身影，从丰富而优美的图片中，体现了男装从实用到装饰的演变。书中将皮尔·卡丹、乔治·阿玛尼、拉尔夫·劳伦等设计大师和1960年代的街头时尚、朋克和夜店风格作比较，为读者娓娓道来男装欣欣向荣的发展历程。对于研究时尚的学生、服饰历史学家和对男士着装感兴趣的人，本书绝对不容错过。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>A rich, comprehensive collection of images covering the revolution in menswear over the last 100 years with text by fashion historian Cally Blackman. Rare photography and illustrations reveal the elegant tailoring of Savile Row and tough khaki and denim of the uniform and workplace giving way to an exuberant array of styles and colours as the century progresses. Packed with images of Hollywood style icons, the artist personalities of the 1930s and more, the evolution of menswear from practical t</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Laurence King Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100 Years of Menswear</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>男装一百年</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67786">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Aurélie Drouet</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>一直以来，那些才华横溢的设计师所创作的令世人惊叹的作品，很大一部分都来自一些废弃的包装材料，这些是他们眼中的无价之宝，室内设计领域的设计师也不例外。简单的木托盘被循环回收利用起来，经过一些欧洲设计师的奇思妙想，转化为不同的别致独特的家居装置。本书附有大量插图及文字说明，步骤与指示清晰明了，你完全可以自己制作出精美装置。无论是床、书架、台灯还是咖啡桌，每件自制设计作品都配有超清插图、详细步骤以及技巧提示，制作起来非常简单，使你获得满满的成就感。你所需要的就是一些时间和几件基础制作工具，你将为自己的家打造出风格独特、卫生环保、设计性强的家居装置。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Artists have long been inspired by the often  literally  priceless treasure of discarded packing materials, and the field of interior design is no exception. Here, the humble wooden pallet is recycled and transformed to create chic and original pieces of furniture, devised by some of Europes most innovative designers  and, thanks to clear, step-by-step instructions and photographs, now you can build them for yourself. Whether bed, bookshelf, lamp or coffee table, each beautifully photographed pr</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Scriptum Editions</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>100% Pallet From Freight To Furniture: 21 Diy Designer Projects</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67787">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Sandra Salamony, Peter Thomas , Donna Thomas</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>书籍是一种永恒不朽的艺术形式，这种形式流传至今，比以往任何时候都更加富有生命力。当今的艺术家们还在继续探索和发掘书籍的本质及其发展极限。这本精美的藏品中，你可以体验到手工制作书籍的各个细节方面：封面、装订、卷抽、折叠和折纸结构等，以及天然艺术品制作的书籍。你也会在书中欣赏到附有大量精美插图和漂亮文字的扉页，以及采用各式印刷程序而制作的书籍。这本精挑细选的藏品，充溢着心灵手巧的工艺和创造力，收录了大量重要历史作品和现代作品。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>The book is a timeless art form, one that is as alive today as ever before, and artists continue to explore and explode the boundaries of what a book is and can be. In this beautiful collection, you will experience close-up various aspects of hand-crafted books: covers, bindings, scrolls, folded and origami structures, and books made from found objects. You will find richly illustrated and calligraphed pages as well as books created from a variety of print processes. Ingenuity and creativity abo</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Quarry Books</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1000 Artists&amp;#39, Books: A Showcase of Fine Hand-Bound Structures</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>1000本艺术家书籍</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67788">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Charlotte Fiell</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>椅子，相比其他的家具，更能成为设计师们狂热梦想的对象。座位靠背的独特曲线或是腿部的弯曲，椅子的弧度抑或是整个手工艺品的色彩，都反映了每个时代的风格意识。从里特•维尔德(Gerrit Rietveld)和阿尔瓦•阿尔托（Alvar Aalto）到维纳尔•潘顿（Verner Panton），再到伊娃•蔡塞尔（Eva Zeisel），从新艺术派到国际风，从流行艺术到后现代主义艺术，椅子的现象是如此的复杂，需要一本像本书这样全面的参考书：索涅特的弯木椅和霍夫曼的“座位机器”，马塞尔•布鲁尔（Marcel Breuer）的瓦西里椅子以及罗恩•阿拉德（Ron Arad）的前卫扶手椅。书中每页关注一张椅子，以其原有的形式展示，加上其设计者和其本身的传记和历史信息。本书是每一个设计爱好者的盛宴，也是收藏家的必选书目。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>More than any other piece of furniture, the chair has been subjected to the wildest dreams of the designers. The particular curve of a backrest, or the twist of a leg, the angle of a seat or the color of the entire artifact all reflect the stylistic consciousness of each era.
 From Gerrit Rietveld and Alvar Aalto to Verner Panton to Eva Zeisel, from Art Nouveau to International Style, from Pop Art to Postmodernism, the phenomenon of the chair is so complex that it requires a reference work as co</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Taschen GmbH</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1000 Chairs</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>夏洛特•菲尔：1000张椅子</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67789">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Ian Rudge</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>在过去的二十年里，我们的户外空间，如屋顶、阳台或是花园，发生了重大变化。如今，我们把可以利用的室外空间视为户外房间，这促使户外装置设计得到了前所未有的发展。一些户外装置的顶尖设计师，如马塞尔·万德斯（Marcel Wanders），菲利普·斯塔克（Philippe Starck）和罗斯·洛夫格罗夫（Ross Lovegrove），专为户外房间设计了独特的家具和灯光。他们的作品成功的挑战了传统花园设计，引进了新材料的应用，使花园发展了一个新的概念即一种家居装置。本书精选了一千种风格不同的设计，全彩插图，是最好的当代花园设计资料读物。每十章开头，都有一个专访，这些专家都是来自花园设计领域、建筑业、产品设计或是精细工艺领域的顶尖人才。新近最新潮的家具、花园艺术，实用的、奢华的，应有尽有。另外，还附有花园设计网址，并对每一个装置产品进行了详细介绍，无论是对花园设计师还是对当代设计爱好者而言，本书都具有重要价值。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>The way we view our outside space, whether roof terrace, balcony or garden, has changed dramatically in the last 20 years. Today we realise the potential of exterior domestic spaces as outdoor rooms, a fact that has led to an unprecedented growth in design products for outdoor settings. Leading designers like Marcel Wanders, Philippe Starck and Ross Lovegrove have created furniture and lighting ranges specifically for the outside. Their work successfully challenges traditional garden design, dev</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Laurence King Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1000 Designs For The Garden and Where To Find Them</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67790">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Mariana R. Eguaras Etchetto</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书提供了改善家装设计的大量实用创意。本书取用世界各地的设计师和装饰家的作品，加入最新家具和物件设计，是挖掘住宅设计灵感的宝藏，不论是森林中的住宅，还是通风的城市阁楼，抑或是大学生工作室。本书旨在吸引大众读者，为每个对宅装饰感兴趣的人提供了许多有用的创意、技巧、建议、意见和方法，不论是住宅首次装饰还是重新修整。本书开头是空间、灯光、色彩和家具概览，接着全面概述了每个房间的地板铺设、墙饰选择、窗饰处理、色彩定制、合理家具布置以及照明等。全书穿插有“要与不要”小贴士，这本灵感指南甚至还强调了在装饰任何空间时所遇到的最大的设计挑战。书中的精美摄影照片、绘画和信息丰富的侧边栏使得本书成为了室内设计一站式参考指南。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>A plethora of practical ideas for home improvement.  Using interiors created by designers and decorators from all over the world, and incorporating the latest in furniture and object design, this book is a treasure trove of ideas for decorating the home, whether a house in the woods, an airy urban loft, or a post-collegiate studio. Aimed at a general audience, it offers hundreds of useful ideas, tips, suggestions, advice, and solutions for anyone interested in decorating a first-time home or rem</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Universe Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1000 Ideas for Home Design &amp; Decoration</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>1000个家居设计创意</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67791">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Charlotte Fiell</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>与经典版《1000把椅子》并行，此次出版的《1000个灯饰》同样容纳了一千多种灯饰设计。书中以十年为界的编排方式展现了20世纪最有趣的灯光：从Tiffany漂亮的镶铅玻璃灯到20世纪60至70年代全然离谱的灯具设计，再至近年来高科技的LED灯。所有主要的风格尽在其中，工艺、新艺术、装饰艺术、风格主义、现代建筑运动、战后风格、波普、后现代等，640页的大容量为您带来一次灿烂的光亮之旅。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Luminary design of the 20th century

Designed to be a companion to our classic title 1000 Chairs, this edition contains an awesome selection of over 1,000 lights. Presented chronologically by decade are the 20th century s most interesting electric lights, from Tiffany s beautiful leaded-glass shades to completely outrageous designs from the late 1960s and 1970s to the latest high-tech LED lamps. All major styles are represented here Arts &amp; Crafts, Art Nouveau, Art Deco, Modern Movement, De Stijl</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Taschen GmbH</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1000 Lights</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>1000种灯饰</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67792">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Jennifer Hudson</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《1000个新设计2以及到哪里找它们》是对来自世界各地的当代设计进行全面综合概要的一本很棒的书籍。书内有巨大范围的新产品，各章包括：桌椅,沙发和床,存储室,厨房和浴室,餐具,纺织品,照明,电子产品以及其他。书中所涉及作品出自以下国际领先设计师之手，如：康士坦丁•葛切奇（Konstantin Grcic），吉冈德仁（Tokujin Yoshioka），罗恩•阿拉德（Ron Arad），帕特里夏•乌古拉（ Patricia Urquiola）和皮尔森•劳埃德（Pearson Lloyd）等。此外，书中对设计当前发展进行洞察并对所选产品进行了深入研究。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>1000 New Designs 2 and Where to Find Them is a comprehensive roundup of the best in contemporary design, from around the world. It features a huge range of striking new products, chapters include: Tables and chairs, Sofas and beds, Storage, Kitchens and bathrooms, Tableware, Textiles, Lighting, Electronics and more. Works by the leading international designers, such as Konstantin Grcic, Tokujin Yoshioka, Ron Arad, Patricia Urquiola and Pearson Lloyd, are featured, along with commentaries giving </DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Laurence King Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1000 New Designs 2: And Where To Find Them</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67793">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Rebecca Proctor</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>现在，越来越多的人开始关注环保了，因为我们已经意识到我们对地球所作的伤害。但关注环保的同时，并不是就得牺牲好的设计。本书展示了当今生态环保的产品和室内设计，引导读者创作和挑选环境友好型的家装设计。书中收录了1000种最时尚、最环保的家居产品，是不可多得的参考读物。书中介绍的产品是由知名设计师和工作室、新锐设计师以及一些顶级零售商设计的，可供各种产品设计师参考，激发设计灵感。丽贝卡•普克特（Rebecca Proctor）是一名潮流顾问、室内设计师和作家。她曾经为沃思世界时尚资讯网（WGSN）工作，现为i-D杂志的固定撰稿人，她还参与创作了Laurence King Publishing出版社出版的《新鞋：当代鞋款设计》（New Shoes Contemporary Footwear Design）一书。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>As we become only too aware of the damage man has caused to the planet, more of us want to furnish and decorate our homes with products that do not harm the environment. But being sensitive to the environment does not mean you have to sacrifice good design. More and more designers are creating products that are both beautiful and ethical. 1000 New Eco Designs is a showcase of contemporary product design and interior products that are ecologically sound. Informative and visually inspirational, th</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Laurence King Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1000 New Eco Designs And Where To Find Them</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>1000个新型生态设计及其所在地</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67794">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Michael Ochs</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书是有关封面艺术的迷人精选（塔森出版社25周年特别版）。唱片封面是我们这个时代与生活的一个标志。就像光盘里的音乐，唱片封面也表现了诸多主题，比如爱、生活、死亡、时尚和叛乱。对音乐爱好者而言，唱片封面是对于一段时间，一段他们生活中的特定时期的表达。许多唱片封面都成为了艺术品，并同它们所代表的音乐一样著名。比如安迪•沃霍尔(Andy Warhol, 1928-1987)为地下丝绒乐队设计的香蕉封面。这本唱片封面的特别精选集合了1960年代到90年代最佳摇滚乐的专辑封面，包括音乐档案管理员、电台音乐节目主持人、记者和前唱片发行总监迈克尔•奥克斯海量的私人收藏。既是一场回忆之旅，也是对于唱片封面进化史的研究，对这一被忽视的艺术形式进行了全新的审视。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>A fascinating survey of cover art (TASCHEN&amp;#39,s 25th anniversary special edition) Record covers are a sign of our life and times. Like the music on the discs, they address such issues as love, life, death, fashion, and rebellion. For music fans the covers are the expression of a period, of a particular time in their lives. Many are works of art and have become as famous as the music they stand for - Andy Warhol&amp;#39,s covers, for example, including the banana he designed for The Velvet Undergrou</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Taschen GmbH</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1000 Record Covers</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>1000张唱片封面</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67795">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>不论你是正想着要刺一个纹身，抑或只想看看别人为了装饰身体而刺的纹身，本书就是你的最佳选择，让你查阅各种信息。本书是塔森出版社25周年特别版，通过世界各地的纹身设计和图片，详细地探索了这种艺术的历史——从19世纪时的雕刻加工到部落身体艺术，从上世纪20年代的马戏团女演员的纹身设计到经典的自行车运动员的纹身设计——提供了对纹身艺术的深刻见解。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>The art of the tattoo (TASCHEN&amp;#39,s 25th anniversary special edition) Whether you&amp;#39,re thinking of getting a tattoo or just want to see to what lengths others have gone in decorating their bodies, this is the book to check out. This special 25th anniversary edition of Tattoos explores the history of the art worldwide via designs and photos - from 19th century engravings to tribal body art, from circus ladies of the 20s to classic biker designs - giving a fascinating insight into the art of ta</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Taschen GmbH</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1000 Tattoos</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>1000个纹身【塔森出版社25周年特别版】</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67796">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Michelle Galindo (Editor)</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书是建筑系列丛书之一，内容详实，独一无二，精选了1000例极具创新、受人瞩目的建筑项目。文化差异与历史差异，造就了风格迥异的建筑，美国北部、中部和南部在当代建筑领域富有创新性，独树一帜。摄影逼真，每个案例都有文字进行详细解析，另附有覆盖全面的索引。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This volume is part of the successful book series &amp;quot,Collection of Architecture?, an unparalleled resource that presents 1000 outstanding and creative projects from 1000 acclaimed and emerging architects revamping the architectural legacies of the past throughout the Americas. Comprised of varying typologies and split by numerous cultural and historical differences, North, Central and South America offer a plethora of innovative trends in the field of contemporary architecture. Stunning photo</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Braun</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1000 X Architecture of The Americas</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67797">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Joachim Fischer</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>这是一本有关当代欧洲建筑最全面、权威和最新的大全，选取了欧洲大陆上各个地方最具代表性的新的建筑项目。欧洲建筑的多样性得以保证，因为每位建筑师通过高质量的照片和方案只能展示一件作品。本书在选取建筑项目作品时，特别重视确保许多小创意和令人惊讶的建筑作品与人们更为熟悉的项目作品一同展示。媒体评论道：“《1000个欧洲建筑》，正如书名所述，书中囊括了欧洲各地，从冰岛到土耳其包括俄罗斯的1000个建筑，我们希望您能够像我们一样欣赏它们。”</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This is the most comprehensive, authoritative and up-to-date compendium of contemporary European architecture available in one single volume. Projects from all parts of the continent have been selected to create a representative overview of the latest European architecture. The great variety of European architecture is guaranteed because there is only one project presented per architect with high-quality pictures and plans. Particular emphasis has been placed on making sure that many small creat</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Braun</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1000 X European Architecture</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>1000个欧洲建筑</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67798">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Braun</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书是“建筑集锦系列丛书”第二卷，成功展现了欧洲今日酒店的多元化。各式各样的酒店在书中以大量插图、计划图和草图以及简短描述的形式展现。本书通过对其风格、建筑和设计的探索，呈现出欧洲酒店的共同之处与差异部分，涉及酒店类型包括著名的大酒店、时尚商务住宿处、新式青年旅社、超赞乡村住宅、带早餐的浪漫旅馆、奢华酒店以及相当特别的酒店，比如茂密森林中的树屋、由监狱、山洞或特制排水管改造的住处。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This second volume in the series Collection of Architecture that started very successfully with 1000 x European Architecture presents the diversity of European hotels today. The wide range of hotel types is shown with opulent illustrations, plans and drawings as well as a short description. 1000x European Hotels reveals what unites and divides European hotels by exploring its variety with regard to style, architecture and design: famous Grand Hotels, stylish business accommodations, innovative y</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Braun</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1000 X European Hotels</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>1000X欧洲酒店</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67799">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Braun Publishing</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>自2006年出版《1000个欧洲建筑1》以来，建筑界已经经历了一些重大变化：2008年，在一个看似不可阻挡的建设热潮中，银行业危机突然袭击了世界经济，但自2010年以来，建筑界又呈现出一片大好的形势。Web 2.0和社交媒体迅速增加的影响力是对建筑界的一次全新的冲击，建筑界取得了长足的进展。20世纪末对建筑风格的激烈辩论已经消退，现在讨论的焦点是实施过程中品质、材料的性价、特别是生态可持续发展等问题。本书为畅销书《1000个欧洲建筑1》的新版本，通过过去五年里1000个新建筑项目，介绍了这个躁动时期的欧洲建筑文化。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Since the release of 1000 x European Architecture in 2006, the world of architecture has gone through some major changes: in the midst of a seemingly unstoppable building boom the banking crisis descended on the world economy in 2008, but since 2010 a spirit of optimism has taken hold again. A completely new impact for the world of architecture, which is gaining in significance, is the Web 2.0 and the rapidly increasing influence of social media. The vehement debates about style at the end of th</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Braun</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1000X European Architecture</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>1000个欧洲建筑（新版）</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67800">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Braun</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>景观建筑涵盖了整个户外设计的范围，这一领域涉及的范围十分宽广，从露天场所规划、建筑物周边、建筑表面和建筑内部到住宅区或露天自给自足的建筑都有覆盖。地景艺术将大自然视为艺术作品的创作来源。不同地理和社会环境形成的设计创意和有趣的解决方案，能够应用于来自世界各地的1000个项目。虽然主要的焦点是公园和花园，本书仍介绍了许多其他建筑范畴——如绿化外墙、石头花园、纪念馆和水景——的类型。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Landscape architecture covers the entire range of outdoor design: the fascinating scope of this field ranges from open space planning near, on or even inside buildings to self-sufficient creations in residential areas or in the open nature, and Land Art that uses nature as raw material for a work of art. The different geographical and social contexts shape the design of the creative and playful solutions applied to 1000 projects from around the world. While the main focus are parks and gardens, </DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Braun</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1000X Landscape Architecture</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>景观建筑设计1000例</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67801">
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>继之前编绘的格林兄弟和安徒生童话故事插图书籍的成功，我们现在邀请了许多年轻的天才插画师为1001夜中的异国风情故事绘制全新插图。本书将传统的故事和当代风格的画作相搭配，让所有的童话故事爱好者都有机会重新探索这些故事。本书收录了从1001夜中精选的8个故事，分别由不同的设计者绘制插图，因此汇集了各种风格。这些插画师来自不同背景，因此展现出一个多面的图像世界，融合了东西方特色的迷人和新颖之处。与前作一样，这本书每两页也至少会有一幅插图，但区别点在于，这里的大量插图有些会带有情色或暴力因素，因此更适合成人读者。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Building further upon the success of our editions of illustrated fairy tales by the Brothers Grimm and Hans Christian Andersen, we have now asked talented young illustrators to visually update exotic stories from 1001 Nights. The popular combination of the traditional texts with these contemporary images gives all fairy tale fans the opportunity to rediscover these narratives anew.
This book contains eight stories from 1001 Nights, including the familiar adventures of Sinbad the Sailor and Aladd</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Die Gestalten Verlag</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1001 Nights Illustrated Fairy Tales from Thousand and One Nights</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>一千零一夜（插图版）</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67802">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Corinna Kretschmar-Joehnk, Peter Joehnk</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>作为接待和等候的地点，酒店大堂是酒店最重要和优先的区域。这里是顾客最初接触到的地方，这里发生的一切都会极大地影响他们是否愉快地度过这里的时光。如同酒店餐厅和酒吧，大厅是一个放松和交流的地方。本书介绍了101个不同的设计概念，它们由两位著名酒店设计专家科琳娜•克雷奇玛•乔恩克（Corinna Kretschmar-Joehnk）和彼得•乔恩克（Peter Joehnk）创作完成。根据设计遵循氛围的信条，他们发现了世界上最多元化的酒店个体设计解决方案，以营造顾客期望的氛围。书中描绘的大堂、酒吧和餐厅囊括了历史上大酒店的新设计、经济型酒店的创意解决方案以及酒店空间设计获奖酒店。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>As the location for reception and waiting, the hotel lobby is the most important and prestigious area of a hotel. This is where the first contact is made with the guests, anything that happens here has a strong influence on whether their stay will be enjoyable. As with hotel restaurants and bars, the lobby is a place to both relax and communicate. This volume presents 101 different concepts by Corinna Kretschmar-Joehnk and Peter Joehnk, two renowned specialists in the field of hospitality design</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Braun</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>101 Hotel Lobbies, Bars &amp; Restaurants</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>101个酒店大堂、酒吧、餐厅</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67803">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Corinna Kretschmar-Joehnk</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>随着我们的生活加速跟上今天疯狂世界的节奏，真正到达某个目的地的可能性越来越重要。酒店客房就代表着这样一个目的地，在这里旅程和目的地、运动和静止之间的界限是最实实在在的。室内设计师们面临的挑战是设计真正沉静在最固有的内部空间瞬态的房间。本书介绍了101个不同的设计概念，它们由两位著名酒店设计专家科琳娜•克雷奇玛•乔恩克（Corinna Kretschmar-Joehnk）和彼得•乔恩克（Peter Joehnk）创作完成。书中的作品通过分类如度假酒店、城市酒店和海滩酒店进行组织，其中每个作品通过方案、图示以及解释说明性文字进行介绍，揭示了每个设计背后的理念。本书尤其重要的地方在于它直接洞悉了两位专业和十分成功的室内设计师的规划过程。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>As our lives accelerate to keep pace with todays frantic world, the possibility of truly arriving at a destination grows in importance. Hotel rooms represent one such destination where the boundary between journey and arrival, movement and stillness is most tangible. Interior designers are faced with the challenge of creating rooms that allow an authentic stillness in the most inherently transient of interior spaces. 101 Hotel Rooms presents 101 different design concepts by Corinna Kretschmar-Jo</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Braun</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>101 Hotel Rooms</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>101个酒店客房</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67804">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Enrique Metinides, Trisha Ziff</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>101个悲剧是恩里克·麦廷尼德（Enrique Metinidess）为当地报纸和红页（因为血腥的内容），而从自己的犯罪场景摄影中挑选的101件重要影像作品。搭配每幅影像的，还有附加的题解，其中呈现了他对场景的描述，对于人物和接头生活的呈现、家庭的悲剧、罪犯、紧急处理工作人员的英雄主义。精选的摄影作品同时也搭配有最早在报纸上发表时的原图。这些作品由特丽莎·齐夫（Trisha Ziff）编集，她同时也撰写了一篇介绍艺术家生平、作品及特色的文章。本书配套的欧美巡回展览于2011年举行。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>101 Tragedies is Enrique Metinidess choice of the 101 key images from his life photographing crime scenes and accidents in Mexico for local newspapers and the nota roja (or red pages, for their bloody content) crime press. Alongside each image, extended captions give his account of the situation depicted, describing the characters and life of the streets, the sadness of families, the criminals, and the heroism of emergency workersrevealing much about himself in the process. Selected photographs </DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Aperture</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>101 Tragedies of Enrique Metinides</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67805">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Phaidon Editors</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>继《10x10》 (2000年出版）的成功问世之后，《10x10 之二》再次向世人介绍当今世界的新建筑。本书插图极为丰富，由10位在国际范围内极有影响力的评论家、建筑师和策展人共同推举，介绍了100个世界优秀的建筑新秀。按照建筑师姓名的首字母编排，本书汇集了近五年来的250个建筑项目和1500多幅插图，既有新近完工的建筑方案，也有还在施工的建筑、以及竞赛中的单元和研究中的项目。本书旨在展示时下最优的全球及区域建筑设计及最新建筑发展趋势。每个受邀评论家都撰写了相关的文字，并从10个不同文化类型和媒介的角度阐释当今建筑设计的背景和影响。本书还附有所有建筑师和评论家的个人介绍。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Like its successfu1 predecessor 10x10 (published in 2000), 10x10_2 is a comprehensive overview of new architecture today. This generously illustrated volume presents 100 of the world&amp;#39,s most exceptional emerging architects, selected by 10 internationally prominent critics, architects, and curators. Arranged alphabetically by architect, the book features more than 1,500 illustrations and approximately 250 buildings and projects of the past five years, including recently built work as well as c</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Phaidon</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>10x10_2</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>10x10  第二卷</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67806">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Carlos Jimenez, Luis Fernandez-Galiano, Joseph Grima, et al</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书为“10x10”系列第三本，自《“10x10”之一》（2000年）和《“10x10”之二》（2005年）相继大获成功后，费顿出版社隆重推出本系列的第三本——《“10x10”之三：全球百座建筑精选》。编者本次同样邀请了十位国际建筑界最具声望和影响力的人物，请他们各自提名10位全球范围内最出色的新晋设计师。本次出版共收录了100位优秀建筑师的设计作品，1500多幅精选的图片依建筑师首字母排列，共涵盖了过去五年间的约250个建筑项目（含建成和在建），为读者全面展现了近年来全球最卓越的建筑项目。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>10 x 10_3 = the 100 best architects you&amp;#39,ve never heard of. That&amp;#39,s about to change. The work shown in this volume is ambitious, inventive, and ground breaking. These are the architects to watch out for, this is the architecture shaping our cities and towns and changing the way we think about the built environment.  Like its successful predecessors 10x10 (published in 2000) and 10x10_2 (published in 2005), 10x10_3 is a comprehensive overview of contemporary world architecture. This generou</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Phaidon</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>10x10_3: 100 Architects, 10 Critics</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>“10x10”之三：百位建筑新秀</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67807">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Alexandra Alevizatos Kirtley</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>1772年，一群来自费城的手工艺人出版了一本名为《橱柜和椅子的价格目录》的书，这本36页的小册子展示了他们制作的家具，并标上了建议零售价以及家具制造商需支付给工匠的价格。虽然早在1772年以前，工艺价格的标准化已在欧洲和美国出现，但是这本书是历史上第一本正式印刷的家具价格目录。如今，这份珍贵的资料收藏于费城艺术博物馆，书中涵盖了五十六种家具，包括桌书桌、书柜、高衣柜、椅子、沙发、床以及一些特殊用途的桌子等。每一种家具下面都有不同设计风格的选择供参考，并列出三个合理的价位表，分别为用桃红心木或胡桃木为主要木材制作的价格以及需要支付给生产这些原材料的木工所花费的报酬。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>In 1772 , a group of Philadelphia craftsmen published Prices of Cabinet and Chair Work , a thirty-six-page book listing the furniture forms they made along with suggested retail prices and the rates master furniture makers should pay journeymen for particular items. While some standardisation of prices within the craft had occurred in both Europe and America prior to 1772, the Philadelphia publication is the first furniture price book known to have been printed. This single surviving copy, now i</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>ACC Distribution</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1772 Philadelphia Furniture Price Book: A Facsimile</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>1722年费城家具价格目录</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67808">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Natalya Gritsay, Natalya Babina</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>在圣彼得堡冬宫博物馆（The State Hermitage Museum in St. Petersburg）的众多藏品中，有着五百多幅十七、十八世纪的佛兰芒绘画（Flemish paintings），当中不乏有出自鲁本斯、凡•戴克、约尔丹斯、斯奈德斯和特尼尔斯等名家之手的作品。这些画作大部分系由俄国女皇叶卡捷琳娜二世（Empress Catherine II）从欧洲各地收购所得，藏品数量迄今在不断增加。本书为首本完整收录圣彼得堡冬宫博物馆馆藏佛兰芒绘画的英文专著，涉及艺术家多达140多位，每幅作品均附有详细的索引和出处信息，堪称佛兰芒绘画黄金时代的生动写照，读者亦可籍此一览俄罗斯收集史的独特景致。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Among the many treasures of The State Hermitage Museum in St Petersburg is its remarkable collection of seventeenth- and eighteenth-century Flemish paintings - more than five hundred in all - including key works by Rubens, Van Dyck, Jordaens, Snyders and Teniers. Forming the core of the Hermitage&amp;#39,s Flemish collection, these were acquired from all over Europe by the Empress Catherine II. From the foundations laid by her, the collection has continued to develop. The major works have been catal</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Yale University Press</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>17th-18th Century Flemish Painting</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>十七至十八世纪的佛兰芒绘画</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67809">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Valerio Terraroli</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>该系列丛书通过对二十世纪艺术文化刨根究底的跨学科横向分析，提供了对二十世纪和新世纪最初几年艺术现象的全面且与时俱进的研究。这第二卷分析和展现两次世界大战之间艺术生产的巨大差异，不仅将从所谓的“重返秩序”到具象方法（新客观主义、意大利二十世纪、魔幻现实主义）的重振——它是反先锋的，充斥着可塑性的语义价值——纳入考量，还对一个目前已被历史相对化的先锋派，及其第二代艺术家（空中绘画、第二代未来主义）作了相应的审视。此外也对诸如超现实主义等特定现象、极权统治的表达及第二次世界大战的爆发作了考察，旁及欧洲以外尤其是美国开放的环境。编年划分由达达主义在德国的诞生、意大利形而上学运动的建树（1917-1920）和美国抽象表现主义（1943-1945）的展露头角来界定。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This series offers a complete, up-to-date survey of the phenomena of the 1900s and the first years of the new millennium through an original, transversal and interdisciplinary analysis of artistic culture in the twentieth century. The second volume analyses and presents the hugely diverse world of artistic production between the two world wars, taking into consideration not only the environment that took shape in the immediate wake of the First World War, from the so-called &amp;quot,return to order</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Skira Editore</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1920 - 1945 The Artistic Culture Between The Wars</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>两次世界大战期间的艺术文化  1920 - 1945</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67810">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>沈榆，张国新</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《1949-1979中国工业设计珍藏档案》中“……30年中肯定不止这21个产品。值得称道的是，编者在推介中有分析、有比较，还有设计轶事等,他们用10年的时间辛苦收集资料，以这种方式表达了中国应该有人来撰写工业设计发展史的希望，并进行了有益的尝试。其次，我想到现在是否具有写史的条件，包括需要研究、回答些什么问题。比如这本书引发一个问题，新中国前30年即1949—1979年有没有工业设计？如果有，应如何评价？甚至再往前推演，中国1919—1949年工业设计是何状况？对此，设计界过去少有议论。只是强调在我国实行改革开放之初，即上世纪80年代通过学习交流，从发达国家“比较系统”地引进了工业设计的理念和方法。对之前的30年知少议少，对再之前的30年可能无人问津了。上海的朋友说得有道理，追溯历史不是怀旧，是期待超越。如果仅从推进工业设计来看，不研究、回答这些问题似无大碍，但如果有史可读，有史可鉴，对经验汲取、普及知识、激励后人、国际交流等都有重要的意义。所以，我想我们应该着手编写中国工业设计发展史了，因为除了需要，时机也已经成熟，主要是我国已经处于工业化中后期，我国已是世界第二大经济体，工业设计已</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《1949-1979中国工业设计珍藏档案》中“……30年中肯定不止这21个产品。值得称道的是，编者在推介中有分析、有比较，还有设计轶事等,他们用10年的时间辛苦收集资料，以这种方式表达了中国应该有人来撰写工业设计发展史的希望，并进行了有益的尝试。其次，我想到现在是否具有写史的条件，包括需要研究、回答些什么问题。比如这本书引发一个问题，新中国前30年即1949—1979年有没有工业设计？如果有，应如何评价？甚至再往前推演，中国1919—1949年工业设计是何状况？对此，设计界过去少有议论。只是强调在我国实行改革开放之初，即上世纪80年代通过学习交流，从发达国家“比较系统”地引进了工业设计的理念和方法。对之前的30年知少议少，对再之前的30年可能无人问津了。上海的朋友说得有道理，追溯历史不是怀旧，是期待超越。如果仅从推进工业设计来看，不研究、回答这些问题似无大碍，但如果有史可读，有史可鉴，对经验汲取、普及知识、激励后人、国际交流等都有重要的意义。所以，我想我们应该着手编写中国工业设计发展史了，因为除了需要，时机也已经成熟，主要是我国已经处于工业化中后期，我国已是世界第二大经济体，工业设计已</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>上海人民美术出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1949-1979中国工业设计珍藏档案</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>1949-1979中国工业设计珍藏档案</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67811">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Isabella Dôther</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《1969》是Contrasto图片摄影社本季度推出的两本出版物之一，用照片蒙太奇的方式记录下那不寻常的一年。这些照片将人们带回它们诞生之日并回忆起当年照片中的人物。1969年有许多关键词，人类首次登月成功、伍德斯托克（Woodstock）、列侬和洋子、越南战争、电影《毕业生》和《虎豹小霸王》,还有那些当代标志性人物的诞生，例如珍妮弗·洛佩兹（Jennifer Lopez,） 詹妮弗·安妮斯顿（Jennifer Aniston）、 克里斯蒂安·莱特（Christian Slater）和 杰克 ·布莱克（Jack Black ）等。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>1969 is one of two books published this season by Contrasto that presents a montage of photographs from a specific year. The power of these photographs calls to mind the year principal birthdays and highlights its key players. Among the events 1969 records are the moon landing, Woodstock, John and Yoko Ono Lennon? and the VietnamWar, the debuts of Led Zeppelin, Genesis and David Bowie, the films The Graduate, Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid and Easy Rider, and the births of such contemporary </DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>ContrastoBooks</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1969: The Year In Pictures</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>1969:图片中的一年</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67812">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Isabella Dother</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>摄影图片社本季出版了两本书籍，《图释1989》就是其中之一，书中用蒙太奇剪辑法将1989这一特殊的年份以图片展现在读者眼前。这些图片的魅力在于使读者回想起1989年里一些主要的纪念日，并且特别突出了其中的主要事件。1989是具有划时代意义的一年，这一年发生了许多历史性事件，如柏林墙的倒塌，天安门广场事件，捷克斯洛伐克的天鹅绒革命以及艾克森瓦尔狄兹号漏油事件。在全球娱乐界，出现了麦当娜和乔治·迈克这两位风靡全球的歌星，还上映了《蝙蝠侠》、《死亡诗社》和《当哈利遇上莎莉》等经典电影。在体育界，1989见证了路德·古丽特斯以及范巴斯顿斯米兰足球队的成功。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>1989 is one of two books published this season by Contrasto that presents a montage of photographs from a specific year. The power of these photographs calls to mind the years principal birthdays and highlights its key players. 1989 was an epoch-making year, among the extraordinary events that this book records are the fall of the BerlinWall, Tiananmen Square, the Velvet Revolution in Czechoslovakia and the Exxon Valdez disaster, in the world of entertainment, the success of Madonna and George M</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>ContrastoBooks</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>1989: The Year In Pictures</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>图释1989</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67813">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Lürzer&amp;#39,s Archive</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《全球200位最佳广告摄影师 》 系列卷对一些全球顶级广告摄影师给予了全面的概述，自2004年始发以来一直广受创意总监、艺术总监、广告文案和广告行业艺术品买家的一致好评，且销量持稳上升。书中入选摄影师先经过主编迈克尔•温捷特（Michael Weinzettl）和安妮•罗丝•斯舒伯恩（Anne-Rose Schlutbohm）(曾为《职业摄影师》出版商)共同预选，然后再由比利时广告创意大师克里斯托弗•吉尔伯特（christophe gilbert）等众多国际知名广告摄影大咖组成的专业评审组筛选评出，因此最终入选者都为公认的全球最杰出广告摄影师。本系列书籍第六卷将于2013年10月面世，届时欢迎读者们前来精选书店、书摊或亚马逊网站上购买。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>The &amp;quot,200 Best Ad Photographers worldwide&amp;quot, series of volumes, each of which boasts more than 400 pages, was first launched in 2004. Published biannually, the highly regarded title has seen a steady rise in sales figures since its launch. The volume is particularly popular with creative directors, art directors, copywriters, and advertising industry art buyers since it provides them with a comprehensive market overview of the world&amp;#39,s best advertising photographers.Following preselect</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Lürzer GmbH</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>200 Best AD Photographers worldwide 14/15</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>全球最杰出200位广告摄影师14/15</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67814">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Jean-François Bizot</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>这本图文并茂的精心怀旧之作，向读者介绍了60年代及70年代在欧洲及美国发表的另类杂志的鼎盛时代的盛况，并重现了杂志中的部分图像。这些杂志既具开创性又晦涩难解，他们通过文化、政治及社会途径不断发挥重要影响。对任何复古绘画迷及对60年代反主流文化着迷的读者来说，本书都绝对不能错过。
本书作者让Jean-Francois Bizot1944年出生在法国巴黎,学习经济学。在十八世纪六十年代反主流文化发展高潮时达到法定年龄。1970年,他创立了法国地下杂志《Actuel》。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Packed with words and graphics, this nostalgic tour de force illustrates and celebrates the 60s and 70s heyday of alternative magazine publishing in Europe and America, reproducing images from magazines both seminal and obscure whose influence continues to reverberate through culture, politics and society. It will be a must-buy for retro graphics fans and for anyone interested in ?60s counterculture.</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Thames &amp; Hudson Ltd</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>200 Trips from the Counterculture: Graphics and Stories from the Underground Press Syndicate</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>反文化的200次旅程：来自地下出版组织的图像和故事</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67815">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Valerio Terraroli</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本系列第五卷，通过分析迷人却备受争议的当代艺术现象，为这个非同寻常的出版项目作了总结。该卷延续了前面四卷的结构，即由大量影像、重要的当代评论家所撰文章和最多样的客体与主题的机巧排列。不过不同的是，它放弃了历史和主题的重构与对最熟悉的人名及科学分类的参考，对科学分类而言，由于其真正的本质，它不可能是主观的。本书紧随日益变化的事件，描述了当今时代的多面向趋势。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>The fifth book in the series, this volume concludes this extraordinary publishing project by analyzing the fascinating and controversial phenomena of contemporary art. Volume V maintains the structure that characterizes the four previous publications, namely a spectacular gallery of images, essays by major contemporary critics and the clever juxtaposition of the most diverse objects and topics. In contrast, it abandons the historical and thematic reconstructions and reference to the most familia</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Skira Editore</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>2000 and Beyond: Contemporary Tendencies</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>2000年及其后：当代趋势</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67816">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Mike Baron and Bernard Chang</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>中国漆器过去多数收藏在各机构和博物馆中，极少有私人收藏。要做一个大型综合性展出可不是个容易的任务。我们找到了能够处理好这个主题的合适人选。胡世昌医生是东方陶瓷学会的常任理事和热心支持者，他曾为1990年在科隆东亚艺术博物馆举办的李汝宽先生（东京）家族收藏中国漆艺展做过编目。李汝宽的家族藏品可能是世界上最大最好的中国漆艺收藏，在将他的藏品带到本次展览中这件事上，胡先生起了重要作用。一家之主李先生今年90多岁，是这个领域的收藏先驱，以他在鉴赏力方面的远见而备受尊重。胡先生本人也是公认的香港漆艺收藏先驱，我们有机会在展出中看到他的许多藏品。胡先生得到了妻子Dorcas的大力支持，我们对她在展览组织方面的帮助表示感谢。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Chinese lacquer has mostly been collected by institutions and museums in the past，while relatively few pieces have found their way to private collectiOns．A comprehensive presentation of a broad spectrum is not an easy task．Dr．Hu Shih—chang lS a long—standing member and an ardent supporter of the Oriental Ceramic Society and in him，we have found the essential scholar to tackle the subject，having made a catalogue of the Lee Family Collection(Tokyo)of Chinese Lacquer exhibition　at the Museum of Eas</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>The Gallery</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>2000 years of Chinese lacquer</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>Catalogue of an exhibition jointly presented by the Oriental Ceramic Society of Hong Kong and the Art Gallery, the ... Kong, 24th September to 21st November, 1993 [Mandarin Chinese]</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67817">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>龙瑞，舒建新</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>书收录车鹏飞、孙海峰、邹明、胡应康、方学晓、庄小雷、吴迅、桂行创、王学辉、朱松发、张复兴、黄定初、王永亮、许钦松、陈风新、梅墨生、帅安、刘昆、何首巫、崔振宽、石大法、刘罡、何家安、常朝晖、石峰、刘朴、周松、董继宁、白云乡、刘皓、周石峰、谢永增、包信源、李明、郑伯劲、程健、吕绍福、李桂泱、郑征泉、熊红钢等40位画家作品。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>河北教育出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>2005中国画研究院年度提名展作品集:山水卷</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>2005中国画研究院年度提名展作品集:山水卷</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67818">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>丁国兴</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《2010-2012中国最美的书》讲述了书籍是人类最古老的记录历史、传递信息的载体。在现代数字媒体诞生之前，人类的科技、历史、艺术无一不依赖书籍得以交流和传承。中国的书籍出版有着悠久的历史，书籍的装帧形式也随着材料和印刷工艺的发展而不断演变。从竹简、木牍成为真正意义上的书，再到纸张以及印刷术的发明，中华民族对书籍形式的探索极大地促进了思想文化的传播，同时传统的书籍设计作为艺术的一个方面，也自立于世界民族之林。近代以来，西方文明传入中国，促进了中国出版与印刷的现代化，中国的书籍设计随之展现了传统与现代结合的时代风格，涌现了一大批优秀设计家和作品。从历史上看，上海是中国现代出版业的发源地，海纳百川，中西合璧，使上海形成了比较重要的文化现象，产生了两方面的出版功能。一方面，它作为原创地，向全国提供丰富的图书,另一方面，各地的出版家和设计家也在上海这个舞台展现自己的才华。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《2010-2012中国最美的书》讲述了书籍是人类最古老的记录历史、传递信息的载体。在现代数字媒体诞生之前，人类的科技、历史、艺术无一不依赖书籍得以交流和传承。中国的书籍出版有着悠久的历史，书籍的装帧形式也随着材料和印刷工艺的发展而不断演变。从竹简、木牍成为真正意义上的书，再到纸张以及印刷术的发明，中华民族对书籍形式的探索极大地促进了思想文化的传播，同时传统的书籍设计作为艺术的一个方面，也自立于世界民族之林。近代以来，西方文明传入中国，促进了中国出版与印刷的现代化，中国的书籍设计随之展现了传统与现代结合的时代风格，涌现了一大批优秀设计家和作品。从历史上看，上海是中国现代出版业的发源地，海纳百川，中西合璧，使上海形成了比较重要的文化现象，产生了两方面的出版功能。一方面，它作为原创地，向全国提供丰富的图书,另一方面，各地的出版家和设计家也在上海这个舞台展现自己的才华。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>上海人民美术出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>2010-2012中国最美的书（平装本）</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>2010-2012中国最美的书</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67819">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>厐薰琹</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书收录庞薰琹、丘堤、庞均、籍虹、庞铫祖孙三代人的作品数百余幅，是一本风格各有所异又统一的精美画册。 庞薰琹先生一生从事美术教育工作，并坚持绘画创作，数十年如一日。主张艺术必须立足于本民族的传统，又不断吸收、融化和创新。擅长油画、水彩及白描，尤精图案和装饰艺术设计，本次选入的先生画作恬静有力，可谓一生代表之佳作,丘堤女士是庞薰琹的夫人，也是中国第一代女友画家，业余爱好是建筑设计与服装设计，她的作品受后期印象主义影响，洗练、大胆，透出东方女性沉静、优雅的气质。庞均先生是庞薰琹之子，也是徐悲鸿先生的关门弟子。身为油画家，庞均教授认真钻研古典与现代艺术，并巧妙地将西方油画语言融合东方水墨写意，形成了独树一帜的艺术风格，被评论家称为“写意性油画”。庞均、籍虹伉俪作为庞氏艺术传承的第二代人，深受浓厚家学的影响，在艺术表达中积极探索油画创作中的内涵与心境表达，这是中国传统文化积淀在西方绘画形式中的融合与创造。庞铫是庞先生的孙女，、她的设计师经历让她的作品用非具象的符号、色块、对象、媒材架构和层叠出一个想象的空间。个人的情感和记忆，经由在创作的过程中和画面的互动而被记录下，理性的作品一直蕴藏在作品的</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>本书收录庞薰琹、丘堤、庞均、籍虹、庞铫祖孙三代人的作品数百余幅，是一本风格各有所异又统一的精美画册。 庞薰琹先生一生从事美术教育工作，并坚持绘画创作，数十年如一日。主张艺术必须立足于本民族的传统，又不断吸收、融化和创新。擅长油画、水彩及白描，尤精图案和装饰艺术设计，本次选入的先生画作恬静有力，可谓一生代表之佳作,丘堤女士是庞薰琹的夫人，也是中国第一代女友画家，业余爱好是建筑设计与服装设计，她的作品受后期印象主义影响，洗练、大胆，透出东方女性沉静、优雅的气质。庞均先生是庞薰琹之子，也是徐悲鸿先生的关门弟子。身为油画家，庞均教授认真钻研古典与现代艺术，并巧妙地将西方油画语言融合东方水墨写意，形成了独树一帜的艺术风格，被评论家称为“写意性油画”。庞均、籍虹伉俪作为庞氏艺术传承的第二代人，深受浓厚家学的影响，在艺术表达中积极探索油画创作中的内涵与心境表达，这是中国传统文化积淀在西方绘画形式中的融合与创造。庞铫是庞先生的孙女，、她的设计师经历让她的作品用非具象的符号、色块、对象、媒材架构和层叠出一个想象的空间。个人的情感和记忆，经由在创作的过程中和画面的互动而被记录下，理性的作品一直蕴藏在作品的</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>文化艺术出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>2011: 艺术传承与升华</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>2011: 艺术传承与升华</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67820">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>台北市立美術館</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>「台北美术奖」自2001年开办以来培育许多视觉艺术创作人才，是为台湾当代艺术重要指标竞赛展之一，多年来累积的成果加上不仅展现了台湾当代艺术的多元与精彩更反映了时代的潮流与变迁，成为新一代艺术创作者展现个人实力与潜力的重要舞台。《2012台北美术奖》共计13名参赛者进入决审资格。评审团至展览现场依据参赛者作品内涵及呈现结果选出「台北美术奖」1名朱骏腾，获奖金新台币55万，并可于两年内提个展计划经审核后于北美馆展出。同时也选出「优选奖」5名李欣哲、周育正、许怡慈、庄哲玮、陈云，各获奖金新台币12万元，其余庄荣哲、黄彦超、杨子弘、刘玗+吴思嵚、蔡士弘、戴翰泓、罗智信为「入选」。即日起至2013年3月10日止，本馆地下二楼开放《2011台北美术奖》展览，邀请大家共同欣赏13位艺术新秀的精采创作。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>「臺北美術獎」自2001年開辦以來培育許多視覺藝術創作人才，是為臺灣當代藝術重要指標競賽展之一，多年來累積的成果加上不僅展現了台灣當代藝術的多元與精彩更反映了時代的潮流與變遷，成為新一代藝術創作者展現個人實力與潛力的重要舞台。《2012臺北美術獎》共計13名參賽者進入決審資格。評審團至展覽現場依據參賽者作品內涵及呈現結果選出「臺北美術獎」1名朱駿騰，獲獎金新台幣55萬，並可於兩年內提個展計畫經審核後於北美館展出。同時也選出「優選獎」5名李欣哲、周育正、許怡慈、莊哲瑋、陳雲，各獲獎金新台幣12萬元，其餘莊榮哲、黃彥超、楊子弘、劉玗+吳思嶔、蔡士弘、戴翰泓、羅智信為「入選」。即日起至2013年3月10日止，本館地下二樓開放《2011臺北美術獎》展覽，邀請大家共同欣賞13位藝術新秀的精采創作。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>台北市立美术馆</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>2012臺北美術獎</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>2012台北美术奖</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67821">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>彼得·布劳恩</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《2013/2014世界名表年鉴》详尽地介绍了150多个品牌超过1300款手表的基本信息，包括设计商和生产商的联系方式、网址、创立时间、员工数量、年产量、销售方式以及经典款式和价格区间，而且还含有他们的发展历史以及所设计出的手表的基本风格和款式。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《2013/2014世界名表年鉴》详尽地介绍了150多个品牌超过1300款手表的基本信息，包括设计商和生产商的联系方式、网址、创立时间、员工数量、年产量、销售方式以及经典款式和价格区间，而且还含有他们的发展历史以及所设计出的手表的基本风格和款式。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>北京美术摄影出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>2013-2014世界名表年鉴</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>2013-2014世界名表年鉴</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67822">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Charles R. Hajdamach</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>这是目前已出版的有关20世纪英国玻璃艺品的图书中最全面的一本，其中囊括了许多迄今为止从未出版过的目录、当代摄影图片和几百件玻璃艺品分类，用以帮助收藏家辨别。绝大多数来自私人和公共收藏的艺品物都是第一次出版。书中包括了从新艺术派和装饰艺术杰作到现在经常被忽视的派热克斯玻璃烤盘，以及雕刻、宝石玻璃和镇纸玻璃艺品中的各种作品。内容聚焦在两次世界大战的影响，特别介绍了包括凯斯·穆雷（Keith Murray）在内的设计师，包括1951年英国节上所举办的重要展览也进行了充分讨论。传记部分介绍了包括杰弗里·巴克斯特（Geoffrey Baxter）、罗纳德·斯坦内特-威尔森（Ronald Stennett-Willson）和弗兰克·斯洛尔（Frank Thrower）在内的战后设计师。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This is the most comprehensive book yet published on twentieth century British glass with hitherto unpublished catalogues, contemporary photographs and hundred of objects grouped to assist collectors with identification. The majority of the items, from private and public collections, are illustrated for the first time. The book covers everything from Art Nouveau and Art Deco masterpieces to the now much ignored Pyrex ovenware and everything in between from engraving, cameo glass and paperweights</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Antique Collectors&amp;#39, Club Ltd</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>20th Century British Glass</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>20世纪的英国玻璃艺品</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67823">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Edmund de Waal</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>陶瓷艺术一直都与新艺术运动同步发展，有时甚至起主导作用，从新艺术运动、装饰艺术、包豪斯和未来主义，历经抽象表现主义、波普艺术和行为艺术，再到大地艺术和装置艺术。从东方主义和色彩理论到现代主义、后现代主义，以及20世纪末期丰富多样的表现手法，本书囊括了欧洲、斯堪的纳维亚、俄罗斯、美国和日本等地区和国家的陶瓷艺术。考量了诸多独特艺术家的作品，包括塔克西勒•都特、克拉丽斯•克里夫、苏茜•库伯、伯纳德•利奇、野口勇、汉斯•科佩尔、露西理惠、胡安•米罗、毕加索、彼得•沃克思和阿德里安•萨克斯等。本书也对陶瓷在其他领域的使用给予了密切关注：雕塑家如安东尼•葛姆雷和托尼•克拉格，甚至建筑师如弗兰克•盖里，陶瓷在他们的艺术实践中也都曾扮演过重要角色。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Ceramics have kept pace with - or even led - new movements in art, from Art Nouveau, Art Deco, the Bauhaus and Futurism, through Abstract Expressionism, Pop and Performance, to Land Art and Installation Art. From orientalism and colour theory to modernism, postmodernism and the profuse diversity of approaches that has characterized the end of the 20th century, this book covers Europe, Scandinavia, Russia, the USA and Japan. The work of exceptional individuals is appraised - including Taxile Doat</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Thames &amp; Hudson Ltd</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>20th Century Ceramics</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>20世纪的陶瓷艺术 （艺术世界）</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67824">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Andrew Casey</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>20世纪给新的收藏家们提供了种类繁多的收藏品，如咖啡杯具、晚宴用品、装饰性的瓷片、鸡蛋杯，甚至是夜壶等大量欧洲和美国陶器产业制造的新式陶制品。收藏品市场在近20年里，也得到了极大的扩张，很多人从当地的跳蚤市场、汽车后备箱市场及拍卖行，买回自己的第一个藏品。网上的拍卖网站如eBay给人们提供了更多的机会购买和出售陶器。本书主要面向那些对20世纪的制陶业感兴趣的收藏家，不论你只关注特定的制造厂的设计师，如克莱丽斯•克里夫（Clarice Cliff）,或者是某一类商品，如面包架、鸡蛋杯或者保鲜罐。本书作者是安德鲁•凯西，她是20世纪制陶业的专家。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>The twentieth century offers the new collector a wide range of opportunities to build up a collection, from coffee sets, dinner wares, decorative plaques, egg cups and even chamber pots to a whole range of novelties that were manufactured by the pottery industry across Europe and America. The market for collectables has expanded greatly over the last twenty years with many people starting to buy their first examples from local flea markets, car boot sales and auction houses. More recently new op</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Antique Collectors&amp;#39, Club Ltd</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>20th Century Ceramics</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>20世纪的制陶业</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67825">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Alison A. Nieder</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>从伞裙到迷你裙，从晨礼服到便装，男士和女士服装设计演变如此之快，以至于你所能做的就是跟随和保持潮流。每个十年里都会出现特定的时装、短期的时尚和时尚信号。近几十年来，复古成为了一种时尚，设计师们不断在现代灵感中加上过去的元素。本书包括吉姆•海曼(Jim Heimann)收藏品的500多个广告，这些1900年至1999年的时装广告带领读者回顾那个定义、重新定义并重新复制时装的世纪。本书附有大量插图，以十年为单位，书中的简介、章节中的文字和年代表探索了时装的主要趋势——从专门产业到大众市场。书中主要介绍的有历史事件、关键杂志、电影和大众文化的影响以及重要的趋势、品牌和零售商。不论你是精通打扮者还是时装业余爱好者，这本视觉历史书籍会提供全面了解20世纪时装风格进化的指南。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Passion for fashion. Between the first decade of the 20th century, when women were still locked into figure-shaping corsets, to the last years of the millennium, when sexy sweats and low-rise jeans became must-have status items, fashion evolved from a luxury enjoyed by the highest echelon of society to a global business that whisks trends off the runway and into the stores before the last supermodel has left the catwalk. From full skirts to miniskirts and morning coats to leisure suits, men&amp;#39,</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Taschen GmbH</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>20th Century Fashion: 100 Years of Apparel Ads</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>20世纪的时装：服装广告一百年</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67826">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>John Peacock</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>自古以来，收集珍贵宝石是帝王君侯的特权。但第一次世界大战后，随着欧洲帝王的陨落，皇家珠宝流转到各界精英手中，这些人包括银幕名流和活跃于暴富阶层社交活动中的各圈名人。11位巨富的迷人女性在20世纪早中期收藏了惊人珠宝首饰，本书对她们进行了介绍。本书二位作者皆为国际珠宝专家，他们披露了珠宝及其收藏者背后的故事。他们不仅生动地再现了这些女性所处的环境，也详细地描述了珠宝本身，生动再现了当时重要珠宝设计师的作品。本书配有珠宝的特写镜头，及一流的初始设计图，还收录了由比顿（Beaton）、霍斯特（Horst）等当时知名摄影师所拍摄的这11位女性的照片。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>For many centuries the collecting of precious jewels was the preserve of kings and queens, emperors and maharajahs. But in the aftermath of the First World War, with the fall of several European monarchies, royal gems passed into the hands of a different kind of elite that included celebrities from the silver screen and a coterie which revelled in a new-rich social whirl. Eleven of these rich and glamorous women, who built up astonishing jewelry collections in the early and mid-20th century, are</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Thames &amp; Hudson Ltd</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>20th Century Jewelry &amp; The Icons of Style</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>20世纪珠宝首饰和时尚偶像</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67827">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>John Peacock</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>多年来约翰•皮科克（John Peacock）一直担任BBC电视台高级服装设计师。他的主要著作包括《时尚资料大全》、《1066年至今服装》、《西方服装的编年史》、《二十世纪时装》、《自1900年以来时尚》、《时尚配饰》、《鞋》、《男装时尚》、《二十世纪珠宝》和其他许多作品。据古董巡回秀的珠宝专家杰弗里•穆恩称，这本书对每个学生和珠宝收藏家来说，不论他们的兴趣或预算怎样，必不可少。本书历经二十年才完成，书中有超过1500种颜色，附有从1900年到2000年间各种风格的珠宝的插图，每张图片都有一个完整的描述。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This book - according to the Antiques Roadshow&amp;#39,s jewelry expert Geoffrey Munn - is &amp;#39,an essential for every student and collector of jewelry, irrespective of their particular interest or budget&amp;#39,. Featuring over 1,500 colour, specially commissioned illustrations of all kinds and styles of jewelry from 1900 to 2000, the book is arranged in 20-year sections, with every picture accompanied by a full description.</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Thames &amp; Hudson Ltd</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>20Th Century Jewelry: The Complete Sourcebook</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>二十世纪珠宝资料大全</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67828">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Paul Carter Robinson</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>铅锡合金（pewter）用途广泛，兼具可塑性和光泽，自古代以来即用于制做各种室内物品（通常为餐具），直至十八、十九世纪，瓷器和玻璃才取代了铅锡合金成为餐具原料。然而，作为白银的廉价替代物，铅锡合金在二十世纪又大放异彩，在全球范围内广泛运用于从建筑到日常物品等领域，尤其是装饰板、家具、花瓶和碗，其灵活的材料属性不断鼓励着设计师尝试新的样式。本书系首本专注于该主题的专著，梳理了铅锡合金自新艺术运动到现代主义期间的发展状况、艺术家和制造商，重点强调了德国、英国、法国、荷兰、奥地利、斯堪的纳维亚、日本和美国等地的主要工厂和车间的历史、商标和印章等细节。作者不仅挑选了350多幅二十世纪优秀铅锡合金作品设计的照片，更分享了有关修复、护理、生产和赝品的宝贵信息。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Pewter is a versatile alloy which has been used to make a wide variety of domestic objects since antiquity. Malleable and lustrous, it was commonly used for making tableware until the eighteenth and nineteenth centuries, when porcelain and glass became more popular. An inexpensive alternative to silver, it re-emerged as a popular material in the twentieth century, allowing for a new-found flexibility, and encouraging designers to experiment with form. From architectural finesse to the smallest e</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Antique Collectors&amp;#39, Club Ltd</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>20th Century Pewter: Art Nouveau to Modernism</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>二十世纪的铅锡合金：从新艺术主义到现代主义</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67829">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Reinhold Mißelbeck, Marianne Bieger-Thielemann, Gérard A. Goodrow, Lilian Haberer, Ute Pröllochs, Anke Solbrig, Thomas von Taschitzki, and Nina Zschocke</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>这本是是20世纪摄影界不可或缺的圣经。摄影开始于一个半世纪以前，但是直到现在才被认可为一门独立的艺术。科隆路德维希博物馆是首个展出大量国际摄影的第一个当代艺术博物馆。书中所描述的尚格鲁伯收藏品是德国最具代表性的藏品之一，也是该博物馆的镇馆之宝。这本书展现了对藏品丰富的多样性的深刻洞察，从概念艺术到抽象主义再到报告文学，所有的20世纪发生的主要运动和流派都从这本书中对20世纪最杰出的照片选集中体现出来的。这边书从安塞尔•伊士顿•亚当斯到彼德•兹瓦特，超过850个作品按照字母顺序被编辑，并且有对照片的描述和摄影家的介绍，提供了一个全面的和不可缺少的二十世纪摄影概述。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This is the indispensable bible of photography in the 20th century. The history of photography began over a century and a half ago, but only relatively recently has it been fully recognised as a medium in its own right. Cologne&amp;#39,s Museum Ludwig was the first museum of contemporary art to devote a substantial section to international photography. The L. Fritz Gruber collection, from which this book is drawn, is one of the most important in Germany and one of the most representative anywhere in</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Taschen GmbH</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>20th Century Photography</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>20世纪摄影</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67830">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Diana Ibanez Lopez, Zofia Trafas, Richard Anderson, TERRAinteralia, Phaidon Editors</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书第一次在一本书中集合了从1900-1999年的世界众多建筑精品。涉及到的超多750座重要建筑都可谓是区域性的地标式杰作。书中的作品按照世界的六个区域进行划分，由150多位业内专家经过严格的层层筛选而得出。所有的建筑都附有完整的插图和简短的文字介绍。此外还有诸如建筑师的实践活动和延伸索引等大量有价值的信息，并用大量翔实的数据揭示出在不同经济和政治背景下一个世纪的建筑变迁。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>The Phaidon Atlas of 20th Century World Architecture portrays, for the first time in one volume, an overview of the finest built architecture from around the world completed between 1900 and 1999. The unprecedented global scope of this collection of over 750 key buildings juxtaposes architectural icons with regional masterpieces. Divided into six world regions, the collection is the result of a rigorous selection process and the input of more than 150 specialists from around the world. Each buil</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Phaidon</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>20th-Century World Architecture: The Phaidon Atlas</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>二十世纪世界建筑：费顿图集</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67831">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>费顿出版社</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《20世纪世界建筑》是“费顿图集（Phaidon Atlas）”系列丛书中的建筑卷，全书首次忠实再现了20世纪世界建筑的杰出成就。与此前以西方建筑为主的权威性视角不同，本书以地理分布的方式进行介绍，全面而细致地展现了757个建筑作品。《20世纪世界建筑》一书旨在为所有读者深入浅出地介绍建筑相关的知识。每个建筑作品均配有实景照片和技术图纸，包括建筑平面图、剖面图和立面图。每个建筑还附有一段简短的文字说明，帮助读者理解其地理特征和文化背景。此外，还附注有客户姓名、地理坐标，并在同一建筑师的不同建筑作品之间进行交叉索引，对相关建筑类型进行分析。在全书最后附有完备的索引，可以通过建筑名称、建筑师、建筑公司等多种方式进行查阅或交叉检索，能够帮助读者更好地进行阅读和查找。全书包含了：132个独立住宅,2个社会住房,2个新城,44个办公建筑,12个银行建筑,9个工厂建筑,2个证券交易所,36个博物馆建筑,48个大学建筑,14个学校建筑,9个市政厅,12个医疗建筑,4个发电厂,5个游泳池,38个教堂建筑,9个人体育建筑,12个酒店建筑,9个机场建筑。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《20世纪世界建筑》是“费顿图集（Phaidon Atlas）”系列丛书中的建筑卷，全书首次忠实再现了20世纪世界建筑的杰出成就。与此前以西方建筑为主的权威性视角不同，本书以地理分布的方式进行介绍，全面而细致地展现了757个建筑作品。《20世纪世界建筑》一书旨在为所有读者深入浅出地介绍建筑相关的知识。每个建筑作品均配有实景照片和技术图纸，包括建筑平面图、剖面图和立面图。每个建筑还附有一段简短的文字说明，帮助读者理解其地理特征和文化背景。此外，还附注有客户姓名、地理坐标，并在同一建筑师的不同建筑作品之间进行交叉索引，对相关建筑类型进行分析。在全书最后附有完备的索引，可以通过建筑名称、建筑师、建筑公司等多种方式进行查阅或交叉检索，能够帮助读者更好地进行阅读和查找。全书包含了：132个独立住宅,2个社会住房,2个新城,44个办公建筑,12个银行建筑,9个工厂建筑,2个证券交易所,36个博物馆建筑,48个大学建筑,14个学校建筑,9个市政厅,12个医疗建筑,4个发电厂,5个游泳池,38个教堂建筑,9个人体育建筑,12个酒店建筑,9个机场建筑。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>人民美术出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>20世纪世界建筑</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>20世纪世界建筑</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67832">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>陈湘波，许平</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《20世纪中国平面设计文献集》分“国民·生活、人民·英雄、公民·时代”三个部分，以20世纪中国三个重要历史时期为时间节点：国民·生活——西风东渐时期以十里洋场为特色的平民文化的市井性,人民·英雄——社会主义建设时期中国宣传的社会性,公民·时代——改革开放以来设计的商业性。邀请了十余位中青年学者对其进行了较为系统的研究，这些图像与文字从一个独特的视角勾勒出20世纪波澜壮阔的时代画卷。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>《20世纪中国平面设计文献集》分“国民·生活、人民·英雄、公民·时代”三个部分，以20世纪中国三个重要历史时期为时间节点：国民·生活——西风东渐时期以十里洋场为特色的平民文化的市井性,人民·英雄——社会主义建设时期中国宣传的社会性,公民·时代——改革开放以来设计的商业性。邀请了十余位中青年学者对其进行了较为系统的研究，这些图像与文字从一个独特的视角勾勒出20世纪波澜壮阔的时代画卷。</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>广西美术出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>20世纪中国平面设计文献集</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>20世纪中国平面设计文献展Documentary of the 20th Century Chinese Graphic Design</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67833">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Gareth Williams</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《21世纪英国的21个设计师》展示了那些自千禧年后开始占据突出地位，居住和工作于英国的设计师们。他们领导了公共趣味和批评性争论,他们是新材料或新流程的革新家和探索者,他们正在建立新的工作方式。结合访谈和评论，加雷斯·威廉姆斯（Gareth Williams）审视了设计的意义和设计一直以来在英国和英国身份方面的象征意义。设计师或设计机构包括佩卡姆盾桌（El Ultimo Grito), 工业设施（Industrial Facility）， 亚米·海因（Jaime Hayon）等,他们为品牌如英国航空公司、 露营者（Camper）、 楚格设计（Droog）、无印良品（Muji）、自然科学博物馆（The Science Museum）和现代艺术博物馆（MoMA）等工作。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>21 , TWENTY ONE showcases designers living and working in Britain who have come to prominence since the millennium. They lead public taste and critical debate, they are innovators and explorers of new materials or processes, they are establishing new ways of working. Combining interviews with commentary, Gareth Williams examines what design means and has meant to Britain and British identity. Designers include El Ultimo Grito, Industrial Facility, Jaime Hayon, Troika, and rAndom International, w</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Victoria &amp; Albert Museum</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>21: Twenty One: 21 Designers for 21st Century Britain</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>21世纪英国的21个设计师</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67834">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Jeremy Meyerson</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>新世纪的工作环境是怎样一副模样？《创意办公室》的作者再度倾情打造，书中囊括全世界各种类型的办公建筑和办公室装潢，对办公环境首次展开全面调研。在科技迅猛发展的今天，社会发生了很大的变革，一切都变得更有效率、更有条理，与此同时，办公环境也经历着革新，新型的办公模型在构想和设计上变得更有创意。在本书导言部分，作者对办公室从20世纪注重科学管理，流水线式的机械模型到21世纪重视空间，要求更加完善的组织功能以及对办公材料更严苛的标准的转变进行了探讨。在随后的4个主题章节中，通过全球45个案例研究介绍了办公室的主流趋势。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This first comprehensive survey of workplace design for the new century, this book captures emerging themes and ideas in office architecture and interiors around the world. Written and researched by the authors of The Creative Office, it advances the concept of increasing creativity in planning and design by exploring the new workplace models that are developing in response to rapid organisational, social and technological change. In the introduction the authors discuss how the new workplace of </DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Universe Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>21st Century Office</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>21世纪的办公室</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67835">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Sarah Howgate, Sandy Nairne， Jo Higgins， Andrew Graham-DixonAn</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书旨在探讨人物肖像画表现手法在21世纪的发展趋势及委托创作肖像画长久以来的魅力所在。编者从全球范围内遴选出了50位艺术家创造的150多幅前沿作品，并将“身份认同”这一备受艺术界关注的概念贯穿其间。书籍内容按主题划分为他画像、自画像、委托与名人画像、社会画像、地缘政治与民族认同、身体、创意作品七大主题。入选的艺术家包括卢西安•弗洛伊德，张洹，马克•奎恩，铃木智明和加文•特克等人。除了展现当代艺术家在肖像画创作上的多种手法，书内更有名家文笔梳理当代肖像画的历史传承，随附阅读书单，为读者深入研究提供方向。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>With over 150 illustrations from fifty artists, 21st Century Portraits explores new developments in the representation of the human form and face as well as the continuing appeal of commissioned portraiture.
The selection of portraits features cutting-edge new work from the international art community, and reflects an increasing interest in identity worldwide. Organised thematically, the book examines seven key strands of portraiture: Observational Portraits, Self-Portraits, Commissioned and Cel</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>National Portrait Gallery</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>21st Century Portraits</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>21世纪肖像画选集</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67836">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>John Wood</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>纯粹之美、视觉和文学观点有条不紊的结合使《21世纪》成为史上最强烈、精致和华丽的精装杂志。杂志第一、二期采用精美的三色印刷，推出由众多著名当代摄影艺术家的作品，并伴有全球著名评论家、学者和诗人们的评论文章、散文和诗歌。《21世纪》通过汇集其他出版物无法涵盖的众多文章和图片，阐明、推广并启发读者，跨越各种文学和视觉的界限产生剧烈共鸣。这个独一无二的宝库汇聚了文化交流、评论和震撼人心的优美图像，是任何严肃的摄影书库或摄影收藏必备的图书。本期介绍的摄影师包括汤姆•巴里尔（Tom Baril）、约翰•达格代尔（John Dugdale）、亚瑟•特雷斯（Arthur Tress）、井津建郎（Kenro Izu）、亚当•弗斯（Adam Fuss）、乔伊斯•田纳森（Joyce Tenneson）、维克•穆尼斯（Vik Muniz）、罗伯特•帕克•哈里森（Robert Parke Harrison）等。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Sheer beauty, combined with the articulate melding of visual and literary points of view, make 21st the most robust, sophisticated and luxurious hardbound journal of the arts ever created. Volumes I &amp; II of 21st feature exquisitely printed tritone images by many of the most respected photographic artists working today complemented by critical essays, prose and verse from some of the world s best known critics, scholars and poets. 21st resonates across a wide range of literary and visual boundari</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Leo &amp; Wolfe Photography Inc</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>21st: v. 2: The Journal of Contemporary Photography</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>当代摄影杂志：21世纪（第二期）</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67837">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Peter Zec</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《21世纪珠宝设计师》是对当代珠宝设计和制造的一项调研。从西方世界的大设计师扎尔（Jar）、詹姆斯•德•纪梵希(James de Givenchy)和尼古拉斯•瓦尼（Nicolas Varney）到东方世界的米歇尔•翁（Michelle Ong）、华莱士•陈（Wallace Chen）和巴加特（Bhagat），本书探索了设计师的世界，帮助读者了解世界知名设计师设计的珠宝，对各类设计师的访谈则揭露了他们的设计灵感和热情、钟爱的材料、设计过程以及他们的个性对设计的影响。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>21st-Century Jewelery Designers: An Inspired Style is a stunning survey of the contemporary jewelery that&amp;#39,s being designed and created across the world today. From the great JAR, to James de Givenchy and Nicholas Varney in the West, and Michelle Ong, Wallace Chan and Bhagat in the East, 21st-Century Jewelery Designers: An Inspired Style is an exploration into the designers&amp;#39, worlds, helping the reader to discover the jewels that great jewelery artists are creating now. Interviews with eac</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Antique Collectors&amp;#39, Club Ltd</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>21st-Century Jewellery Designers: An Inspired Style</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>21世纪珠宝设计师：</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67838">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Arnd Friedrichs</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>可堆叠塑料椅遍布在日常生活的各个角落，露台、庭院、小吃店或是露营地，尽管设计爱好者对其嗤之以鼻，但它仍旧是世界上最成功的一件家具作品。本书对此做了有趣详细的研究，重新解构了这件褒贬不一的作品。书中收录了知名设计师菲利普·斯塔克（Philippe Starck）、泽西·西摩（Jerszy Seymour）、马丁·巴斯（Maarten Baas）、康士坦丁·葛切奇 （Konstantin Grcic）的作品，并挑选了与这把椅子有关的大量摄影艺术作品，以一种荒诞、戏谑的角度审视这个现象。书名来源于制作这把椅子的工艺流程——聚乙烯在220℃的高温下捣碎，再通过模具机挤出而成。本书由设计师昂德·费里德里西斯（Arnd Friedrichs ）和克斯汀·芬格（Kerstin Finger）联合编写，克斯汀的上一部作品《胶带》也让我们领略了他非凡的创造力。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Aesthetic reconciliation with the world&amp;#39,s most successful piece of furniture. It can be found on patios and in yards, snack bars and campgrounds around the globe. Although despised by design aficionados, it is arguably the most successful piece of furniture in the world. 220 C Virus Monobloc is an entertaining documentation of the love-hate relationship designers have with this chair. In addition to homage paid by renowned designers including Philippe Starck, Jerszy Seymour, Maarten Baas, an</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Die Gestalten Verlag</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>220°C Virus Monobloc</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>220℃病毒体</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67839">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Maren Eichhorn-Johannsen</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书由马尔恒•艾希霍恩•约翰森（Maren Eichhorn-Johannsen）和阿德莱德•哈什（Adelheid Rasche）合作完成，以柏林国家博物馆（Staatliche Museen in Berlin）的丰富藏品为基础，回顾了珠宝从旧石器时代以来两万五千百年间的发展。作者通过将珠宝与文化、时代相联系，为我们展现了其设计、佩戴和收藏的演变过程。书中内容以年代为序，收录了多篇短文与近四百幅插图（均附详细文字说明），汇集的珠宝作品多为首次出版，当中既有项链、戒指、耳环等经典种类，也有源于非欧洲国家的罕见种类，包括古希腊王冠、巴比伦金耳环、十三世纪伊斯兰皇室项圈、普鲁士王后路易丝的系列收藏、勒内•拉利克设计的新艺术风格珠宝，以及当代设计师的作品，实为对文化史、珠宝史和珠宝制作工艺感兴趣者的必备之选。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This opulent book reaches back 25, years to trace the history of jewelry from the Paleolithic era to the present day. Drawn from the extensive holdings of the Staatliche Museen in Berlin, this collection of jewelry through the ages links cultures and eras to show how the design, wearing, and collecting of personal adornment has evolved over the ages. Many of these beautiful pieces are presented for the first time in book form. They range from classic items such as necklaces, rings, and earrings </DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Prestel Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>25,000 Years of Jewelry</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>二万五千年之珠宝史</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67840">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Gabrielle M Finn</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书用不超过半分钟的时间，向你介绍50个最重要的人体结构和系统知识。本书“30秒”系列畅销书的其中之一，让读者从一个全新的角度去学习那些他们认为需要很花精力才能了解的课题。每一个标题都涉及一个流行的话题以及围绕它的50个核心概念。每一个概念，无论多么复杂，都只用两页纸，300个字和一幅图片加以解释，使人们能够在半分钟内消化这些知识。本书让你迅速了解人体是如何运作的。无论你是一个医学院学生、艺术家、身体工作者又或是一个仅仅想知道你的医生在说些什么的人，本书都是一本实用的速查手册。书中涉及许多前沿的生物和解剖学研究，布克和海尔们（电影《布克和海尔》2010中的偷尸贼）绝对不能错过。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>The 50 most important structures and systems in the human body, each explained in half a minute. The bestselling 30-Second series offers a new approach to learning about those subjects you feel you should really understand. Every title takes a popular topic and dissects it into the 50 most significant ideas at its heart. Each idea, no matter how complex, is explained using a mere two pages, 300 words, and one picture: all easily digested in only half a minute. 30-Second Anatomy offers you an ins</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Ivy Press</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>30-Second Anatomy</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>The 50 Most Important Structures And Systems In The Human Body, Each Explained In Half A Minute</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67841">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Edward Denison, Jonathan Glancey</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>书中用简练的文字，向你介绍50个最重要的建筑法则和风格。本书30秒系列畅销书的其中之一，让读者从一个全新的角度去学习那些他们认为需要很花精力才能了解的课题。每一个标题都涉及一个流行的话题以及围绕它的50个核心概念。每一个概念，无论多么复杂，都只用两页纸，300个字和一幅图片加以解释，使人们能够在半分钟内消化这些知识。这本书给你关于建筑的基本知识，对于撰写本书的专家级作者们是一个巨大的挑战，他们要去解释的不仅仅是建筑赖以存在的原则，更是这些原则在实际运用后产生风格效果，为读者上一堂形式和功能融为一体的速成建筑课程。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>The 50 most significant principles and styles in architecture, each explained in half a minute. The bestselling 30-Second series offers a new approach to learning about those subjects you feel you should really understand. Every title takes a popular topic and dissects it into the 50 most significant ideas at its heart. Each idea, no matter how complex, is explained using a mere two pages, 300 words, and one picture: all easily digested in only half a minute. 30-Second Architecture presents you </DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Ivy Press</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>30-Second Architecture</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>The 50 Most Signicant Principles And Styles In Architecture, Each Explained In Half A Minute</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67842">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>伊莉莎·威廉姆斯</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>严选30支经典创意广告独家揭露制作背后不为人知的成功秘笈。配以大量图片揭示广告的发展脉络、创意背景等其他幕后花絮。阿迪达斯、可口可乐、斯柯达、索尼等超级品牌广告创作细节大揭底。给您提供制作点击率过亿的广告创作灵感，轻松做数字爆炸时代的弄潮儿。《30支经典广告案例》带领读者进入广告业幕后，向我们展示了近10年来30个杰出的广告大片。无论是对业内专业人士还是对广告制作过程感兴趣的人来说，《30支经典广告案例》都颇具吸引力。它不仅涵盖了广告制作的技术信息，而且还记录下创意人员、导演以及客户的一些轶事，并且详尽地呈现了广告的制作过程以及所遇到的问题。每个广告片经历了不同阶段，包括草图、早期的创意被否定、故事板、有声动画、照片以及广告的最终拍摄。《30支经典广告案例》中的经典广告包括：阿迪达斯经典三叶草 家庭聚会、可口可乐 耶耶耶 啦啦啦广告、尊尼获加 行走于世的男人、微软Xbox 蚊子,香槟、斯柯达 烘烤广告、索尼PLAYSTATION 游戏的过去,游戏的未来，等等。每一支都经典的值得收藏和品味。《30支经典广告案例》中每支广告的特点是配以大量的图片来揭示它的发展脉络，包括故事板、拍摄的照片以</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>严选30支经典创意广告独家揭露制作背后不为人知的成功秘笈。配以大量图片揭示广告的发展脉络、创意背景等其他幕后花絮。阿迪达斯、可口可乐、斯柯达、索尼等超级品牌广告创作细节大揭底。给您提供制作点击率过亿的广告创作灵感，轻松做数字爆炸时代的弄潮儿。《30支经典广告案例》带领读者进入广告业幕后，向我们展示了近10年来30个杰出的广告大片。无论是对业内专业人士还是对广告制作过程感兴趣的人来说，《30支经典广告案例》都颇具吸引力。它不仅涵盖了广告制作的技术信息，而且还记录下创意人员、导演以及客户的一些轶事，并且详尽地呈现了广告的制作过程以及所遇到的问题。每个广告片经历了不同阶段，包括草图、早期的创意被否定、故事板、有声动画、照片以及广告的最终拍摄。《30支经典广告案例》中的经典广告包括：阿迪达斯经典三叶草 家庭聚会、可口可乐 耶耶耶 啦啦啦广告、尊尼获加 行走于世的男人、微软Xbox 蚊子,香槟、斯柯达 烘烤广告、索尼PLAYSTATION 游戏的过去,游戏的未来，等等。每一支都经典的值得收藏和品味。《30支经典广告案例》中每支广告的特点是配以大量的图片来揭示它的发展脉络，包括故事板、拍摄的照片以</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>北京美术摄影出版社</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>30支经典广告案例：从创意到实现</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>30支经典广告案例：从创意到实现</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67843">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Lannoo Publishers</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>1914至1918年期间，为重新瓜分世界和争夺霸权，欧洲强国在世界范围内发起了一场大规模的战争，史称第一次世界大战（World War One）这场战争以萨拉热窝事件为起点，以德军战败、同盟国投降而告终，是世界历史发展的一个重要转折点。本书共收录了365张极具历史意义和收藏价值的一战老照片，为读者呈现彼时战火纷飞的西线战场前沿和军队在壕沟日常生活的独特景观，带领读者重回那早已远去的战争岁月，反思战争带来的灾难与破坏。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>In 1919 publishing company Van Cortenberg published photographs from World War One with the title &amp;quot,Never Let Us Forget&amp;quot,. Those pictures were sold as postcards for the benefit of widows and orphans. This book collects these photographs together, 365 images at the western front of World War One give the reader a unique view of the battlefield and the daily life in and around the trenches: wounded people, soldiers relaxing, arms, ammunition factories with civilians, guards, cold winters, </DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Editions Lannoo sa</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>365 Images 1914-1918</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>365张一战摄影作品：1914-1918</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67844">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>3xn Architects</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本专著规模宏大、装订精美，以在科学与艺术、标志性设计与融入周遭环境之间探索的丹麦建筑实践为主题，丰富的文字信息包含了超过25个工程和项目，并附有评论文章、案例研究以及采访记录。收入本书的建筑物既有丹麦驻柏林大使馆、弗雷斯德学院和利物浦博物馆之类的高规格建筑，也有像路易斯安那州展馆和NOMA实验室之类的小型项目，基本涵盖了丹麦建筑工作室迄今为止的全部建筑作品。博•玻杰•拉尔森和卡斯帕•古尔答格•约根森为本书撰写了精彩文章，让•安穆德森、金•赫尔弗斯•尼尔森和阿伦•卡加尔•安徒生均在受访之列。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This massive, beautifully rendered monograph on the Danish practice known for creating architecture in the nexus between science and art, between iconic design and context, is packed with information covering more than 25 works and projects, critical essays, case studies and interviews. From high-profile buildings like the Danish Embassy in Berlin, Ørestad College and the Museum of Liverpool to smaller projects like the Louisiana Pavillion and NOMA Lab, the entire spectrum of the offices accompl</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Archilife</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>3XN Architects</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>3xn 建筑师</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67845">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Nicholas R. Bell</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书系为庆祝伦威克画廊（Renwick Gallery）成立四十周年而专门出版，由尼古拉斯•贝尔（Nicholas Bell）编著，精心挑选了四十位年龄均不超过四十岁的艺术家，以表彰其创作的作品改变了整个现代工艺的面貌。书中回顾了工艺理念在传统媒介（如陶瓷和金属制品）及雕塑、工业设计、装置艺术、时尚和可持续生产等领域的演变。尼古拉斯坚信工艺的传承乃是一套灵活的工具，而非一僵硬的结构，并在书中展示了年轻艺术家们是如何打破界限、扩展概念框架，从而树立起工艺在当代艺术和文化界的重要角色。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>In this beautifully illustrated volume, published in celebration of the Renwick Gallery&amp;#39,s fortieth anniversary, author Nicholas Bell highlights forty artists (all under the age of forty) actively engaged in creating objects that are transforming contemporary crafts. &amp;quot,4 Under 4&amp;quot, investigates evolving notions of craft within traditional media such as ceramics and metalwork, as well as in fields as varied as sculpture, industrial design, installation art, fashion, and sustainable manu</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Yale University Press</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>40 Under 40: Craft Futures</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>四十位年轻艺术家作品选集：工艺的未来</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67846">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Paul Goldberger, Joseph Evan</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>格瓦斯美•斯格尔（Gwathmey Siegel）的作品无疑代表了20世纪末期至21世纪早期现代建筑的巅峰。本书着重介绍屡获嘉奖的建筑公司格瓦斯美•斯格尔 &amp; 联合建筑事务所设计的一个重要作品，即位于纽约曼哈顿中城区第五大道400号的斯台第五大道酒店，它高达60层，内部设有各层次集舒适实用和奢华典雅于一体的独立产权公寓客房，并配有世界一流的五星级酒店服务，可谓曼哈顿市中心独一无二的建筑地标。本书作者保罗•戈德伯格（Paul Goldberger）曾于1997-2011年间担任《纽约客》的建筑评论家，并为该杂志具有很高声望的“The Sky Line”专栏写作，于1984年荣获普利策杰出评论奖。现任《名利场》撰稿编辑，同时在曼哈顿新学院任设计和建筑系Joseph Urban主席。合著者罗伯特•西吉尔（Robert Siegel）则是格瓦斯美•斯格尔 &amp; 联合建筑师事务所的首席建筑设计师，也是该公司的联合创始人。他专注于公共与学术建筑的创新，研究兴趣集中在可持续建筑设计领域。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Gwathmey Siegel&amp;#39,s buildings represent the pinnacle of late-twentieth and early-twenty-first-century modernist design, and this new volume focuses on a single architectural masterpiece: 400 Fifth Avenue. Designed by the award-winning architectural firm Gwathmey Siegel &amp; Associates Architects and soaring sixty stories above Fifth Avenue, 400 Fifth Avenue seamlessly integrates an unparalleled collection of spectacular condominium tower residences with the world-class, five-star Setai Fifth Aven</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Rizzoli  Publications</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>400 Fifth Avenue: Gwathmey Siegel: A new Gwathmey Siegel Landmark</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>第五大道400号</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67847">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Natalie Rothstein</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书由娜塔莉•罗斯坦（Natalie Rothstein）撰写，全面回顾了西方时尚服饰400年来的生动历史，是同类型书籍中的经典之作。书中共有插图一百二十幅，作品均来源于维多利亚与阿尔伯特博物馆（Victoria &amp; Albert Museum）中无与伦比的服装系列收藏，包括十八世纪乔治二世（George II）的宫廷礼服、英国服装品牌维维恩•韦斯特伍特（Vivienne Westwood）的现代海盗系列和福塔尼、波烈、查尔斯•詹姆斯及约翰•加利亚诺等当代顶尖设计师的作品。此外，书中还有大量衣物配件（如鞋子、扇子、帽子等）的精美图片。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Now with a new jacket, this breathtaking overview of 400 years of Western dress is a lively history of fashion that stands as a classic in its field. With 120 illustrations, the book is a visual delight that draws on the V&amp;A’s unrivaled apparel collection. From a dress worn at the court of George II in the 1700s to Vivienne Westwood’s contemporary Pirates Collection, to pieces by leading designers such as Fortuny, Poiret, Charles James, and John Galliano, this book is an outstanding resource tha</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Victoria &amp; Albert Museum</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>400 Years of Fashion</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>四百年时尚史</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67848">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Sebastiano Brandolini, Ernesta Caviola</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>5只侧身的企鹅，加上1只正面企鹅像——这幅如此奇怪的图片却是一个建筑事务所的标志。它们没有自然的保护、没有厚重的铠甲，只有小心谨慎。这样一种看似好玩而令人不安的注视，使得这类地理位置遥远的鸟类看上去离奇而有趣。在萨沃纳，该事务所的建筑师们勇气非凡但达不成共识的选择（他们本可以成为极简抽象艺术派艺术家，就像出身优越的小孩），把他们自身拖进了第一场政治争论。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Five penguins in profile and one head on, what an odd image to represent an architectural agency. No natural protection, no armoured skin, but discretion and an amusing and disquieting gaze that makes those geographically distant birds seem so quaint. In Savona, in the Fornaci Promenade, their courageous, non-consensual choice (they could have chosen to be minimalist like the children of good families that they are) dragged them into their first political argument - See more at: http://www.skira</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Skira Editore</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>5 + 1: The Shadow of Ideas</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>5+1：创意的阴影（斯基拉建筑学图书馆）</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67849">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Isabel Kuhl, Kristina Lowis, Sabine Thiel-Siling</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书由巴塞罗那艺术史学家伊萨贝尔•库尔（ISABEL KUHL）、柏林国家博物馆艺术史学家克里斯提娜•罗伊斯（KRISTINA LOWIS）和艺术史学家、编辑撒比尼•希尔•思玲（SABINE THIEL-SILING）合作完成，为读者简要介绍了自文艺复兴以来的五十位建筑大师，以此追溯过去六百年间的主要美学运动，展现了这些大师们的才华。从菲利波•布鲁内莱斯基到安东尼•高迪，再到弗兰克•盖里，从跨页彩色插图到信息丰富的文字描述，再到贯穿全书的时间表，这本简明易懂的建筑史将引领读者纵览全球、穿越历史，了解这些塑造了不同阶段建筑史的大师们所运用的多种手法。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Starting with the Renaissance, this introduction to fifty visionary architects traces the major aesthetic movements over the past six centuries and offers concise portraits of the geniuses behind them. This accessible and lively survey takes readers around the world and through history, from Filippo Brunelleschi to Antoni Gaudi to Frank Gehry. It contains double-page spreads that feature full-color illustrations, informative sidebars, and a timeline that extends throughout the book. A concise an</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Prestel Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>50 Architects You Should Know</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>你应当知道的五十位建筑师</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67850">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Thomas Koster, Lars Roper</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书由记者、作家、编辑托马斯•科斯特（Thomas Koster）和自由撰稿人、旅行作家、策展人拉尔斯•罗珀（Lars Roper）合作完成，收录了五十位主要的艺术家及其代表性作品。每一条目均以十分醒目的样式加以呈现，包括了简要传记、时间发展概要、评论分析、重要术语表和相关艺术运动、技艺链接。此外，作者也提供了充足的信息，帮助读者迅速在网上和博物馆找到对应艺术家的作品。书中内容以年代为序排列，精选而出的五十位艺术家基本涵盖了自哥特时期以来的主要艺术运动与发展，能使读者清楚地了解到视觉艺术的演变过程。本书既适合休闲阅读，亦能做简单的参考之用，相信会是人人喜欢、乐趣与实用兼备的一门艺术史课程。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This vibrant reference guide profiles 5 major artists alongside their representative works. The entries are presented in an eye-catching format that includes brief biographies, time lines, and critical analyses. Additional information helps readers locate the artist&amp;#39,s work online and in museums, a glossary of important terms, and sidebars highlighting relevant movements and techniques. Arranged chronologically, the selection of artists includes every major artistic movement and development s</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Prestel Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>50 Artists You Should Know: From Giotto to Warhol</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67851">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Lucinda Hawksley</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书由艺术、旅行作家露辛达•霍克斯利（LUCINDA HAWKSLEY）撰写，信息丰富、可读性高，收录了五十位最优秀的英国艺术家（包括布雷克、班克斯、特纳和翠西•艾敏等），以展现英国艺术五个世纪的主导地位和卓越成就。书中既有托马斯•庚斯博罗和斯坦利•斯宾塞的宏伟肖像画、特纳和大卫•霍克尼的景观画，也有威廉•霍加斯和吉尔伯特-乔治组合的讽刺画、亨利•摩尔和雷切尔•怀特瑞德的雕塑，以及雷森•佩里和达明•赫斯特的最新作品。每位入选艺术家均以双页篇幅加以介绍，内容包括其最具代表性的作品、作品细节、简要传记以及其人生与时代之深刻洞察。作者将伊丽莎白时代微图画家的技能、维多利亚兴盛时期的宏伟风格与英国战后现代主义者、青年艺术家加以比较，证明后者对争议主题的大胆尝试正是英国艺术传统的辉煌传承。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This roll-call of British artists confirms the dominance and excellence of British art across five centuries, from Blake to Banksy, Turner to Tracey Emin. This highly readable and informative collection of the best of British art showcases magnificent portraits by Thomas Gainsborough and Stanley Spencer, landscapes by J. M. W. Turner and David Hockney, satire by William Hogarth and Gilbert &amp; George, sculpture by Henry Moore and Rachel Whiteread, and the latest works by Grayson Perry and Damien H</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Prestel Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>50 British Artists You Should Know</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67852">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Isabel Kuhl</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>《你不可不知的50座建筑》一书带领读者沿着漫漫时间长河，领略全世界最有趣、最震撼的50座传世建筑。在这里，读者不仅会看到经典的胡夫金字塔、帕特农神庙和罗马斗兽场，还会欣赏到土耳其的圣索菲亚大教堂，柬埔寨的吴哥窟，中国拉萨的布达拉宫以及德国柏林的犹太博物馆。全书以建造时间为顺序，采用全彩图的装帧方式，生动地呈现出建筑相关的信息。在这里，读者可以轻松地了解每个建筑本身的艺术意义，风格形式和当时的风土人情。同时时间表和侧栏的设计也为读者提供了更多建筑周期和技术的说明。作者伊莎贝尔·库尔（Isabel Kuhl)现居德国科隆，作家和艺术史学家。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>The fifty buildings presented here in chronological order represent the most compelling, intriguing, and awe-inspiring structures from all over the world. Along with the Pyramids of Cheops, the Parthenon, and the Colosseum, readers will learn about other masterpieces such as the Hagia Sophia in Turkey, Cambodia&amp;#39,s Temple Complex at Angkor Wat, the Potala Palace in Lhasa, and the Jewish Museum in Berlin. Each entry features full color photographs of the structure along with informative text pr</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Prestel Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>50 Buildings You Should Know</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>你不可不知的50座建筑</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67853">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Christiane Weidemann , Brad Finger</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>了解伟大的当代艺术家是了解当下艺术世界异彩纷呈的绝佳途径。活跃于二战之后的艺术家们面临着一系列的挑战——原有的风格界限被打破、技术愈发先进、性别与种族问题成为了前沿话题。本书收录了20世纪后半叶与21世纪初期各类艺术运动与激烈变化中的五十位优秀当代艺术家，包括画家、摄影师、雕塑家和行为艺术家等。书中内容按时间顺序排列，作者克里斯蒂安妮•魏德曼（CHRISTIANE WEIDEMANN）和布拉德•费格（BRAD FINGER）在整个当代艺术的大背景下，以2-4页的篇幅对每位入选艺术家进行了介绍，在展现其最具代表性作品的同时，亦提供了简要传记、艺术生涯纲要以及主要艺术发展背景，实为一场多元而鼓舞人心的艺术前沿发现之旅。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This survey of great contemporary artists is the perfect introduction to the exciting world of art today. Artists working after the Second World War faced a confounding array of challenges, as stylistic barriers were broken, technology advanced, and issues of sexuality and race came to the forefront. From painters and photographers to sculptors and performance artists, fifty of the most influential contemporary artists are profiled in this colorful and engaging book that traces the various artis</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Prestel Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>50 Contemporary Artists You Should Know</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67854">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Doria Santlofer</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>今天的年轻设计师们比以往任何时候的前辈都更有见识也更加无畏。无论是进入高级服装品牌工作或是未能进入，他们的声誉都受到那些乐于游走在时尚弄潮儿与潮流跟风者之间的精明客户的维护。本书收录的时尚圈中最具创造性、最具代表性的人物既有时装周的常客，也有势头强劲的后起之秀。每一位设计师都占据一个跨页版面，内容包括设计师的T台作品、笔记、草图和生平介绍。书中的五十位男女设计师都已接受了既是挑战也是激励的现实，这个现实既是全球的现状，也有来自经济和环境的考量。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Today&amp;#39,s young designers are savvier and more daring than ever before. Happy to exist within or outside of the established houses of haute couture, their reputations are cemented by savvy consumers who are willing to navigate the thin line between trendsetting and trend following. This book of the most creative and iconoclastic members of today&amp;#39,s fashion scene includes Fashion Week regulars and cutting edge up-and-comers. Each designer is profiled in double-page spreads that include runwa</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Prestel Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>50 Contemporary Fashion Designers You Should Know</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>50款你应该知道的时尚设计</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67855">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Claudia Hellman, Nina Kozel</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>他们塑造了我们的现代生活，无论是我们坐的椅子，或是我们阅读使用的计算机，还是我们生活的房屋。设计无处不在，本书收录了五十位上个世纪最具影响力的设计界人物。从索奈特的第一把弯木椅子，到包豪斯和勒•柯布西耶的整体设计世界，以及设计师的签名样式，如查尔斯和雷•埃姆斯、艾琳•格瑞和菲利普•斯塔克，还有斯沃琪、无印良品、苹果等国际知名品牌，本书中，这些设计师的背景信息、照片和精美的插图以跨页形式呈现。这本鼓舞人心的书籍极具可读性，以独特的方式呈现了这些设计对于我们日常生活的深远影响。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>They&amp;#39,ve shaped our modern age, whether it&amp;#39,s the chair we&amp;#39,re sitting in, the computer we&amp;#39,re reading on, or the house we&amp;#39,re living in. Design is everywhere, and this volume profiles fifty of the most influential figures over the past century. From the first bentwood chairs by Thonet to the holistically designed worlds of Bauhaus and le Corbusier, and from the signature styles of designers such as Charles and Ray Eames, Eileen Gray, and Philippe Starck to internationally-known b</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Prestel Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>50 Designers You Should Know</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>50位你必须知道的设计师</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67856">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Simone Werle</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书由西蒙娜•维勒（Simone Werle）撰写，收录了过去一百年间推动时尚界发展的50位最重要的时装设计师及其最令人难忘的作品，其中既有阿玛尼、普拉达、卡尔文•克莱恩和Dolce＆Gabbana等红地毯常客，也有克里斯汀•迪奥、卡尔•拉格菲尔德和奥斯卡•德•拉•伦塔等经典服饰商。有的设计师为大众而设计（如拉尔夫•劳伦、唐娜•凯伦、黛安•冯•芙丝汀宝），有的设计师则认为品味高于实用（如让•保罗•高提尔、维维恩•韦斯特伍特、赫尔穆特•朗）。翻阅此书，读者既能了解到二十世纪早期创造了时装史的可可•香奈儿和安德烈•库雷热等，亦能一览当下的主要推手，如斯特拉•麦卡特尼、马克•雅可布和汤姆•福特等，相信这本信息丰富、异彩纷呈的时尚参考手册必会满足不同口味、不同年龄之人士。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>The latest volume in Prestel&amp;#39,s most successful series profiles the world&amp;#39,s top 5 designers, including Armani, Balenciaga, Dior, Galliano, Givenchy, Lacroix, McCartney, McQueen, Quant, Versace and Westwood. Their careers and creations are explored through colourful, double-page spreads, with a timeline to highlight significant events in the designer&amp;#39,s life and to outline their accomplishments and influence. Brilliant full-colour reproductions of the designer&amp;#39,s works bring their cr</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Prestel Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>50 Fashion Designers You Should Know</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67857">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Diane Maddex</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>这本由戴安娜•马德克斯（Diane Maddex）所著的新书包含了五十多张极佳的彩色照片，展示了起居室、餐厅、厨房和室内场所，表达了弗兰克•劳埃德•赖特的创新想法，比如创建开放式的楼面布置图以增加宽敞的感觉，使用天然材料将外部的风景带入室内，内置家具设计简化了空间安排，并以强有力的几何形式将它融合在一起。本书为精装书，共128页。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Showcasing Frank Lloyd Wright&amp;#39,s best work in interior design, this volume exemplifies the architect&amp;#39,s principles of unity, simplicity and respect for nature. The rooms featured also represent a chronological picture of his stylistic development. Photographs highlight furniture, fireplaces, lighting, carpets, fabrics, stained glass and china, capturing the essence of Frank Lloyd Wright&amp;#39,s appeal.</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Thames &amp; Hudson Ltd</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>50 Favourite Rooms by Frank Lloyd Wright</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>弗兰克·劳埃德·赖特设计的五十间著名房间</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67858">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Edward van Voolen</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>提起犹太艺术家，普通读者们可能对此知之甚少。《你不可不知的50位犹太艺术家》一书的出版可以说是弥补了这项空白。本书以时间顺序编纂，详细记载了过去两个世纪里全世界范围内最伟大的犹太艺术家。他们大都来自欧洲、北美和以色列，包括十九世纪艺术家大卫·奥本海姆，所罗门·哈特及戈特利布, 极富盛名的现代主义艺术家毕沙罗，莫迪里阿尼和夏加尔，以及摄影师曼雷等。全书装帧精美，提供艺术家简要生平经历和趣闻轶事，并附有大量全彩作品复制图，给读者带来美妙的阅读体验。本书作者爱德华·凡·伍伦（EDWARD VAN VOOLEN）为拉比（犹太教神职人员），艺术史学家和犹太历史博物馆馆长，并撰写了多部有关艺术、建筑和犹太教书籍。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Readers will find much to learn and explore in this beautiful collection of images from the most prominent Jewish artists of the past two centuries. Presented in chronological order, each entry features magnificent reproductions of major and lesser-known works, as well as a brief biography of the artist, compelling stories about his or her work, and relevant historical details. The range of artists includes those from across Europe, North America, and Israel: icons of nineteenth century art such</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Prestel Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>50 Jewish Artists You Should Know</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>你不可不知的50位犹太艺术家</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67859">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Christiane Weidemann</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>从詹姆斯·阿伯特·麦克尼尔·惠斯勒（James Abbott McNeill Whistler）到马修巴尼（Matthew Barney），《你不可不知的50位现代艺术家》一书几乎收录了全世界所有最享有盛名的现代艺术家，向读者生动展示了每一位艺术家挑战传统，重新定义规范的非凡贡献。本书精心设计，全彩图双页装帧，对每位艺术家的生平经历和趣闻轶事进行修订，并提供大量高清作品复制品以飨读者。此外，用不同颜色标记的时间轴贯穿本书，以突出重要的历史时间和事件。从印象派到超现实主义，从立体主义到流行艺术，读者在轻松的阅读中就可完成一场畅快淋漓的艺术享受之旅。本书作者为克里斯蒂娜·魏德曼（Chritiane Weidemann),艺术史学家、作家、编辑。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Starting with James Abbott McNeill Whistler and ending with Matthew Barney, nearly every prominent figure in Modern art is represented in vibrant double-page spreads that show how these artists continued to redefine norms and challenge tradition. Fascinating biographical and anecdotal information about each artist is provided alongside large reproductions of their most celebrated works, stunning details, and images of the artists themselves. A colour-coded timeline spans the entire volume, showi</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Prestel Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>50 Modern Artists You Should Know</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>你不可不知的50位现代艺术家</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67860">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Kristina Lowis</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书精选了七百年间的50幅标志性绘画作品，在提供一节速成艺术史课程之余，其华丽精美的彩色插图也能使读者乐于思考。书中收录了乔托的阿雷纳大教堂壁画、波提切利的《维纳斯的诞生》、达芬奇的《蒙娜丽莎》、维米尔的《戴珍珠耳环的少女》，以及莫奈、梵高、卡萨特、塞尚、达利、卡萝、霍普、波洛克、罗斯科和奥基夫等艺术家，基本涵盖了主要的绘画大师。作者克里斯提娜•洛韦斯（KRISTINA LOWIS）和唐新•匹克拉尔（TAMSIN PICKERAL）均为艺术历史学家，他们所挑选的画作不仅历经了时间考验、大多读者也熟悉，其背后历史也令人着迷。翻阅此书，读者也将了解到画家、作品历史意义和珍藏地点等相关信息，实为了解伟大画作的理想之选。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>Spanning seven centuries, this selection of fifty iconic paintings offers readers a crash course in art history while presenting gorgeous color reproductions that are a pleasure to contemplate. Starting with Giotto&amp;#39,s Arena Chapel frescoes and continuing through Botticelli&amp;#39,s The Birth of Venus, da Vinci&amp;#39,s Mona Lisa, Vermeer&amp;#39,s Girl with a Pearl Earring, as well as works by Monet, van Gogh, Cassatt, Cezanne, Dali, Kahlo, Hopper, Pollock, Rothko, and O&amp;#39,Keeffe, nearly every import</DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Prestel Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>50 Paintings You Should Know</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>你应当知道的五十幅绘画（插图版）</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
  <book id="67861">
    <DC_CR_AUTHOR>Peter Stepan</DC_CR_AUTHOR>
    <DC_DN_CSKETCH>本书介绍了从摄影的初始阶段到现今神奇而具有魔力的相机时代，这期间世界上最伟大的摄影师。这些摄影师，从利克斯•纳达尔（Felix Nadar）到南•戈尔丁（Nan Goldin），每个人都代表了摄影艺术发展的一个关键点，对摄影的发展起着十分重要的作用。本书以跨页的形式呈现每名艺术家，包括艺术家最重要的代表作品、简要的传纪、信息丰富的侧边栏和贯穿本书的时间表。本书综述了摄影师如何持续不断地超越其所在领域的极限，同时给读者提供了认识和了解世界的新方法，是不可多得的绝佳读本。</DC_DN_CSKETCH>
    <DC_DN_SKETCH>This dynamic introduction to the world&amp;#39,s greatest photographers from the inception of photography to today bears proof of the magic of the camera. From Felix Nadar to Nan Goldin, each of the photographers featured here represents an important aspect of photography&amp;#39,s evolution. The artists are represented in double-page spreads that include reproductions of their most important works, concise biographies, informative sidebars, and a timeline that extends throughout the volume. The result </DC_DN_SKETCH>
    <DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>Prestel Publishing</DC_PUBLISHER_HOUSE>
    <DC_TITLE_BOOK>50 Photographers You Should Know</DC_TITLE_BOOK>
    <DC_TITLE_CBOOK>你应该知道的50名摄影艺术家</DC_TITLE_CBOOK>
 </book>
</root>